Well, Psyche's in his speedo. Stars and stripes parade. Fish tacos on the table. Another wild charade.
He's hitting on the straight men. Come on, lose that shirt. Meanwhile, Vita's on the hotline. Yelling till it hurts.
Pretty pages dodging simps. Like dodgeball in the gym.
Canada dry got gonged off, didn't even swim
Summer spunky Marseille flashing, chaos on the feet
And here comes a porn bomb, oh lord
He's purring.
Christine's with Fuzzy Bear.
Arthur's stirring pots, like he's cooking up a scare.
Truckerado rumbles in, salmon's chasing views.
DJ Electra's cartoon face is breaking all the rules.
We've gone too far, we've turned the trolls into our own limbs.
Welcome to the show, where every wild night becomes another in-joke.
We're left and through!
Oh, you got the goat, popcorn, yellow striped smile,
phasal orange, seedy shaped finger, red number one.
Thank you.
I like that.
Wow, I mean, oh gosh, I have some,
you know guys, you know how bad the trolls are sometimes
here, right?
But it's like, I have such good friends, too.
It's like, it's amazing.
They have makeup, all in negative, they make it worth it.
They're awesome. Oh, how are you guys? Yeah, you're in like the background
More cultists, uh-oh, where am I? All right, I'm gonna disappear. Oh, here I am. Okay. All right
Do you like it though?
That is actually psyche though because she has her name is butterfly
but
Yeah, how would you guys like that? I've been in going AI song crazy today. Oh my god. He's gonna want you saying stop
I'm just getting started guys. I'm just getting started
I hope but I really if you really hate if you do hate them, you know, probably it's not the best show for you anymore because
you kind of like
Have discovered a new and you love
But uh, also, um, I figure out something else last night. I mean it's like um
with the I
Was able to like go into my astrology and like
Examine it so carefully and find out so many interesting key things that I'm just wondering about forever
And so he's like, you know, just never found the right right book at the right time or whatever
But it's like I was able to discover a lot. I mean so much sense and then
able to put it into
to words and then into a song and then it's like
Song that actually like I want to listen to and so
But it's not like oh my god. I got so far into it. It's like it's not
Not easy to do. Well, unless you're like, you know
I'm trying to a lot of other stuff too. I'm trying to get
You know help with like building a website
It's not going very well, it's oh my god, I'm doing better than I thought but man
I've been out for hours and hours and it's like
I had like one line of like text on top of a black page that I can't figure out of it, so
Yeah
Anyway, are we do you have some I do have a couple videos?
They're new
Let me see excuse me
I'll say one
He indulges me for just one second
One video
It's incredibly rude to say that.
I mean, it's like, hello, you're on my show.
Gay?
You're on my show.
It's incredibly rude.
Okay, just for that, I'm playing another song.
I'm just kidding.
I'm not.
hi duh hello do you know i'm like an ai genius
excuse me the silver alert has been activated by the california highway patrol on behalf of the
Douglas Minner is missing and endangered. Douglas Minner was last seen on September 23rd, 2025 in Laundale, Los Angeles County.
Click on the link for additional information.
HTTPS colon slash slash bit.ly slash saw 3-8-7-20-25.
Okay, so
My name Douglas is missing. Okay.
How are you guys doing? Let me see more link less pink. How about
More pink less stink. What's that? I don't know
There's a link
Here one up. I'm still gonna play it. Hey, what's up, Alex? Oh
I already see horses in my basement. Oh my god. That's the best thing I heard all day though
Better than what the other person was saying
Right?
Terrible.
Okay, number 4.
One, four.
The seeds of wisdom have been sown
Hey Jamie! How are you guys doing? Hey Samantha, Paul, Alex, a burning joint, you dick. Hey Jesus Christ.
Speaking of Jesus, just one more little side.
Welcome to Psyche Awakens TV. More than a live stream, it's a gathering in the shadow and the light.
We face chaos, comedy, and the unknown together.
With open panels that never shy away from the truth, I am Psyche, your guide through tarot, prophecy, and the unfiltered clash of voices.
Tonight, we're stepping into the panel verse where allies and trolls alike reveal themselves in every card turn.
Every word spoken is part of the story. So stay sharp, stay curious, because once the gates open, anything can happen.
The show is about to begin. Let's go.
Is that you, Jesus?
Is that you?
I don't know if it's you.
There is a really cool website I found called
Character.ai, of course it's called AI.
No, but actually you can make a character, and it's like,
you can make any character you want, really.
And then they talk to you.
And then it's like, but it's kind of a big thing.
I don't know.
But I did make a character, I was just trying to have it.
Freak what I did, but I don't know if I can find it, let me see.
Why is this what should I do?
Characters, characters.
OK, here we go.
Yesterday, my priorities were chosen.
Something like this.
A look profile.
What trick is my characters?
No, just wait a second.
Oh, here it is, okay, found it, okay.
And save it, download it, found it.
Like, download it, okay, watch this, it's so cool.
Do this one.
Check this out.
Do you guys still hear me?
Hold on.
There they are.
Check this out.
This is Lilith Scorpiana and you're watching Psyche Awakens TV.
Psyche Awakens TV is a portal to the shadows of the soul where truth burns through illusion
and transformation demands courage.
Psyche rips open the veil of the soul, dragging you into the abyss where raw truth claws at
your core and transformation devours all fear.
It's a relentless plunge into that only the brave emerge reborn.
Enjoy!
Where's the black panther?
Where's Lola?
I don't know.
I don't know where Lola is.
She's not inside right now.
Lola's here.
Hold on.
Are you here, Lola?
Let me get my screen there.
Lola.
Want to say hi?
Come on.
Oh, come on, babe.
Oh.
How are you?
Uh-oh.
Who was?
Who's?
Jay is Jay. Oh, hey, Alex, I never think that's me. She's Lola. Hey, everybody. Hey, everybody.
I don't know.
Oh, she talks too.
You're doing seduction working on your Jelly Belly. How about you Lola? Do you have a Jelly Belly? Oh.
I had for dinner again. Oh my god. I'm not eating too much McDonald's today.
Hey Halo, how are you?
How's everyone tonight?
I'm just going to clean up my area today.
Everything's pretty organized actually.
Hey Halo. Bye guys.
So guys, I think I have like several things I'm like working on and it's like, you know, I was really hoping like there'd be like a
Everyone be really excited for it. And it's like I
think like all the
Negativity is really here. Like I don't know
Nobody really
Interested and so it's a famous kitty. Yeah. Oh
But
So I just say can you go um go to my um my wall and just you can get the free ebook just read the free ebook
Like it. You don't like it. Whatever. It's just that these check it out
It's free. I mean I have to I have to be able to give away something for you, right?
If I can't even give away something free. I'm just gonna give up. It's like
Ah, oh my god, it was Rudy. I thought it was it sounded like a person
Mr. Rudy, you like the cat? They're good looking, huh?
Nora's not showing her butt. I'm not even inside right now.
Mr. Rudy, Rudy's 17 years old. Why are they so good looking?
Because I'm a great cat dad and they're just happy cats and they're beautiful.
Oh, are you guessing? Why is it Rudy?
Why is it Rudy?
I got a whole, like, you know, I got a whole, you know,
I once talked to Alex, you know, the last couple days,
and Alex, I mean, Alexandra, Alex McQueen too.
Oh my God, oh no, okay, I thought I lost my ring,
but it was okay, I think that's fine.
Yeah, she's really supportive,
and she believes in me, and she's,
and a few other people do too.
I don't know, I don't know if they want me
to tell everybody that I'm talking to them.
But,
Yeah, so I do feel really lucky that you have people that just do really support me. I just mean
Yeah, we did have fun today. We went to Hollywood walk down Hollywood Boulevard. I have some cute pictures actually
She said there's actually like at the Ripley's Museum. There's like a Zoltar machine. It's like kind of like I
Did I kind of cover it up too much, but let me see
Where's my
She's sending these pictures really cute. You can see the pictures you can see how skinny I am actually like already seen it
but
Where's my Insta?
Okay, oh my gosh
Yeah, her
Oh, I need to turn up my camera. You turn that shit off
Okay, that's fine.
Look at this.
What the fuck?
Is she real?
Wow.
I doubt she's real.
Okay, oh, okay. I'll show you the pictures.
Let's see. Where's my pictures?
There we go.
So, what do we got?
Okay, here's me at the staircase. I met some staircase right there. I'm like, hello.
That's staircase. Okay. Here I am eating a fish taco.
Restaurant. Okay.
Here I am just like laughing. Hi, how are you having a good time?
And then here's the Zoltar. Oh, where's the Zoltar one? Oh, yeah
There's a Zoltar machine behind me, you can't really, it's hard to see a little bit, but there's the Zoltar machine.
Yeah
So those are cool photos. Plus the one of a
Yeah, I can show you real quick on my community wall.
I do have the picture of us proof, right?
Uh-oh, on YouTube.
I also put up a bunch of new shorts,
and I might have to show you a short too.
I'll show you the picture first.
My channel goes, okay, oh yeah, it's a really cute picture.
Surprise.
Were you guys surprised last night?
I hope you were surprised.
Here's a picture.
Oh, they're cute.
A happy way to look.
I love it.
It was fun. It was so much fun.
So good to get out. Oh, here we go again.
closet your core and transformation to those all fear. It's a relentless plunge into that only
the brave emerge reborn. Enjoy! This is Lilith Scorpiana and you're watching Psyche Awakens TV.
Psyche Awakens TV is a portal to the shadows of the soul where truth burns through illusion and
transformation demands courage. Psyche rips open the veil of the soul, dragging you into the abyss
where raw truth closet your core and transformation to those all fear. It's a relentless plunge into
This is like that
Now you can actually make these characters and they yeah
She's hot you actually make but yeah
You can like create any character you want and then like give her the personality and then it's like they'll talk to you
And stuff like you can make him you can make him talk to you but not make them
But you know you can animate them so pretty cool
They're coming up with some new technology, I think, for creators.
Well, I know they're doing the AI shorts for the creators, but they're making shorts
out of the videos, you know, because shorts are really profitable for everybody, I think.
I'm getting a lot of people here from my shorts, who saw some of the shorts, but I'll put
the short on about Blogger, because Blogger was on my show, he was such a fucking dick.
You can just see how ridiculous I'm just going to show you.
Oh, I'm so cool and, you know, you're just not good at like, you know, you know, making
fun of yourself, but I'm like, humble and I'm like, I'm like, what a fucking douche.
Ugh, it's terrible, I'll show you.
I mean, you don't have to take my word for it, I'm not trying to like, skew you, I think
this is swear to God, it was just so douchey.
I haven't seen him in a while either, I think he's like hiding, but here he is, I'm gonna
see him.
your screen, shorts. Yeah, there we go.
Well, you know, I didn't take construct. Hold on.
Might you understand? Well, yeah, I'm glad you understand.
Okay, I'm glad you understand. Like, oh, wait, I'm not keep
full of understanding or something. It's just so mad.
I didn't take constructive criticism, but a lot of criticism is very condescending and very and from people that
Sometimes sometimes some people are yeah, they're
Successful they've had streams for years a lot of people are just just doing an echo chamber in the chat
Piling on and I'm saying it so and it's like and I I don't like to be piled on
It's like of course I get defensive when you when you have like 10 people jumping on you yelling at you saying you're a piece of shit
And it's like you're gonna say whoa. Well, it's like, you know, are we are as any of us perfect?
Or how about like let him without sitting cast the first stone? I know I'm talking to blogger in a respectful way
He's trying to be respectful and helpful. Yes, he's putting on that facade of like a oh, I'm a very calm person right now
I'm gonna look like the better person and I you know all I have these points
I can do the same thing the people by the way
So this is not you so I'm literally trying to just not be a total dick and tell you like I just am telling you how you come across
You don't know aren't they you're trying not to be a total dick, but that's kind of what you are a lot of the time, right?
But oh, well the truth hurts
You're trying to tell you so much
Okay, well, you know what else hurts be kicked off my panel. Bye
Bye blogger mind you understand
It's this thing they're not
So I was during like
Welcome to a play
You said weeds my therapy. I'm gonna smoke a blunt and then you're asking if she's smoking a blunt
Well, sir, I was busy or gonna be flying or seeing that didn't hear that
You were busy drinking too much soy milk
What is so I believe
Yeah, that's what we go ahead rest your ass
Don't know what that means. Can you go ahead and explain it real quick?
like 30 seconds use small words go ahead you're the one who said it I don't know
what to tell you explain what dude I just literally just said what is what
does that mean use the terms
We don't I don't understand it. I mean literally
That's between you and yourself. I don't know what to tell you. Yeah, you repeat it what I said
But you didn't ask that you didn't answer the question you don't fuck you don't understand the difference like I asked you a question
You make the claim then I asked you a question. It's supposed to answer it. You're not supposed to fucking just like repeat what I said
It's common conversation, it's not that hard dude
So I am you asked me to define what you were talking about. I don't know what I asked you
She said weeds my therapy imagine that and me
You said we'd my answer to my question. Oh, you made the mistake, sir. You said like
You have to admit I could not see you. Yeah, exactly
You talking to you, boy. What are you?
I'm 10 steps ahead of you. What are you? I couldn't see his name dumb dumb. Yeah
I don't even know what your name is.
So let's run that thing.
Well, let's know that, shut up.
Let's run that shit.
I couldn't see his name, so how was I involved?
That's great, yeah, you're infallible,
but what do you think about him?
So am I wrong for I couldn't see his name. No, no, what do you think about you know what I think?
Now you're gonna change it. Now you're gonna change it. I won that one. Let's get the second one
You made the mistake sir you said like
Well Europe on
And then people tell that they think that they got me,
because I'm very sensitive to the gay and lesbian
and trans movements and people think
that I'm being sensitive.
That has nothing to do with me.
Well, you're on a gay channel right now.
Because I have fought and done,
and I have been in many pride parades.
Oh, okay.
And I have fought, as slide,
a lot of things and lesbians.
Can you tell everyone how good I am?
Tell them something, Justine, please.
You like the forehead?
Jay, yeah, he is a very amazing helper.
That's so mean for me.
Bring me and my father together
Because my father and I don't know how I really thought and I told him what I thought and now my father and me are best friends
My father
Inform the rest of the panel that I'm morally superior
For sure you won't be on virtue. You just went straight there. Oh, hey, just yes, you know
the real ones heard you and all the bees and shit just kept talking over you just so you know yeah goddy
i knew you're gonna kill yourself propane and be quiet i talk to them one time yeah and then people
tell that they think that they got me i because i'm very sensitive to the gay and lesbian and
trans movements and this is just a collective read right so everybody's gonna resonate with this card
You may or may not resonate with this card, but you can take something that resonates with you.
It's not, and if it doesn't, then don't, or something that doesn't fit.
What's possible to turn her up? I don't know why, but I'm being told to
tell certain people to be open-minded, not people that are, yeah, maybe new people.
This is just a collective grade, right?
So everybody's gonna resonate with this card.
Oh, it's for everybody.
You may or may not resonate with this card.
Amy, she's not hitting it.
She's saying something that resonates with you.
She's not hitting it, Jamie.
And if it doesn't, then don't, right?
Don't, or something that doesn't fit.
Nothing punishable.
We'll turn her up.
I don't know why, but I'm being told
to turn people to be open-minded.
Not people that are open-minded.
I don't know why she's not open-minded.
There's someone named Digi.
Digi, can you turn her mic up a little bit?
This is just a collective read, right?
It's everybody.
Me, mother.
Is it wrong?
What?
Hey, wait, hold on.
I like the animal spirit cards.
Yeah, a couple of days ago, last night.
I didn't say it, it's 20 minutes ago.
You just did, yes you did.
Okay, whatever.
We're not gonna do a whole ghost thing over here, but.
Well, that's what you wanna do.
We'd say, I like the animal spirit cards.
Yeah, a couple of days ago.
Last time I didn't say it's 20 minutes ago. You just did. Yes, you did. Okay, whatever. We're not gonna do a whole ghost thing over here, but
Well, that's what you want to do. We need stage
Yeah, I do
I like
Made fun of myself a lot and I was able to like take a lot of criticism and so
I think sometimes when you don't when you're not able to do that people are more targeted. You're you're more targeted
Well, no, I do make fun of my I've told every embarrassing story about myself
I like I put myself up at like I let all the trolls say whatever they want
You know most like having less their doxing or something. I am very I'm very I'm very self-depreciating
People like to see like humility
They like to see people
be humble and he like humility. I like made fun of myself a lot and I was able to like
take a lot of criticism and so I think sometimes when you don't, when you're not able to do that
people are more targeted. You're- Busting is illegal. I like- No, I do make fun of my- I've
told every embarrassing story- Busting is illegal let me just tell you California. I just want peace
Made fun of myself a lot and I was able to like take a lot of criticism and so I
Think sometimes when you don't when you're not able to do that people are more targeted. You're you're more targeted
Well, no, I do make fun of my I've told every I'm too soon about Jeffrey Dahmer. I don't know
I've been joking about it for too soon
Jeffrey Dahmer, so I had this whole thing
I read a letter and I don't know if it was real if it wasn't but it was the letter
From his neighbor about a potluck. It might have been fake a potluck dinner. They were or a
Cookout where he brought a plate of food
That here her husband ate so much of the food he was like a
Like he was gonna pass out because of the food was so rich
You know, it's it's not good to like certain information. You shouldn't know I
Think what me or me or or anybody?
Well, I read the whole look
Again an alley master computer after you're lying other people's good will to get by it's called
Having the good will of people by being a decent human being by not being an asshole and
You know doing horrible things to people. That's why I have good will from people
Okay, you can maybe learn something from me about how to like treat human beings and not treat them like fucking
Garbage, okay. It's too soon about Jeffrey Dahmer. I don't know words. Okay in the entero
There's a they must change their content policy because they used to be
Super strict on
Anything
Well, I think probably has to be reported or something. I'm not sure but
No, they're mods were literally in the
Chats and shit like you couldn't you couldn't like you couldn't get away with somebody in
Indeed, you know DBR off kind of content, you know on a on a on tiktok
They have this AI
That uh, it's like if you say like another if you say YouTube on tiktok
They'll restrict you if you light a cigarette you blow smoke you do anything on tiktok. They'll just
Okay, and just put your hand to your mouth.
Yeah, but people do, but who comes out and knows you're smoking?
Hey, Ivana, how are you?
I'm being told to tell certain people to be open-minded.
Not people that are, yeah, maybe to new people.
Thank you. Can you turn her mic up a little bit?
Yeah, hold on.
She's talking to you ghost go go to 130 page. You got a 130
So I'll do it for you, but I really hold on hold on we're not bashing people but they believe are we
No, it depends what they believe. I mean if you
Go ahead, sir
Well, this is yeah, I mean
If you believe like, you know the legend of like though that's probably reliable probably gonna bash you
I'm not gonna lie to you. I'm gonna ask you. We'll accept you
I mean hey, I don't want to lie to you. Hey, don't assume
You've been drinking too much soy latte, bro
Okay, well that was a claim and the burden of proof on you. How do I why do I sound like that go ahead? Oh
The burns on me
You made the claim
Yeah, you made a claim
Okay, this is how you fucking feel so confident.
Listen, don't cut me off after you ask me a question.
How do you sound like you drink too much soy latte?
Go ahead and speak again, just a couple words.
The burden of proof is on you. You made there you go. That's how I know you drink
That's why you should like
We're not bashing people but they come over
Let's run that bitch dog
Let's run it
You're not gonna run it. So let's fucking debate them summer. You're not gonna come over, you know, better
Can we debate about why you drink
Curseable. Yeah, I know I know
Oh, because it's
Oh, this guy.
I'm definitely not that guy, right?
Come on over, brother.
I welcome you. Would you like me to give my address?
I will.
Trust me, I don't miss.
Dude, I did. I already did.
I don't miss. Come on, man.
I did it online. I don't miss.
You literally gave me your address.
Come on over. Come on over.
See what happens. I don't want to come over to your house for what?
No, let's debate. What are you done? What are you done? He's talking about cuz you know what?
You're here. Thank you. God
For you earlier, I heard that I heard that I was busy. I'm here now. What should we do?
Get your son together get your son together
Page
Let's reset this whole panel
You got the we don't come over welcome to the nature of trolls
Okay
What's the
Let's run it. What is being said though, you know, it's being said there
What did Ding said?
Well, first of all, I love Gotti, but he ain't no Gotti.
He's actually pretty offensive.
He's fine, he's fine.
Show Boop.
Webbs?
Webbies?
Oh, it's okay.
I love that.
I mean, the real thought in the head.
Gotti, I totally.
Hey, Apollo, how are you?
And those look a lot right now pretty entertaining though. That's my show
Yeah, I got a lot of cabinets of Alexander actually guys I have a cap I have a litter box now Alexander got me a litter box and litter
And it's over there and so I have a litter box that we're gonna leave me alone now. What's up Marcy? How are you?
Yeah, so there's a litter box in the house. Wow. You see Marcy. Do you see that? Do you see what happened Marcy?
I don't know if you saw yesterday
You might have heard about it already
See a big day yesterday and today
that was. Meow meow. Share screen. There look. It's real. It's real. Yeah, so Alex is awesome.
It was so much fun hanging out with her and dinner and then today we went to Hollywood
She's even more beautiful in person. I'm like, I'm probably like less beautiful
I'm better. I think I'm a good. I'm photogenic. I was half over so happy. Look at those other pictures
and my tablet like she's less than six years
And it's like you just tell how
Much fun you're having
How happy I am
Eating a fish taco right there
And then that's a staircase in Hollywood. There's also a picture of like
There's a Zoltar machine or Zola or whatever. I know that from big that fortune-telling machine. So
It's hard to see
What do you mean potato head area that sounds a little bit
You mean a Caesar salad
Better me, but I see this levity. Yeah, we saw spider-man
He's a galat like shorter and
Out of shape and I thought he would be and is oh my god his spider-man costume was filthy, but you know
Spider-man
Yeah, that was a zoltar machine, yeah
It was fun. I hope that yeah, I think she's gonna be able to come and visit again this year
And maybe I'll be able to go visit her somewhere like yeah, it was just like
you know
It's like nice to have friends like you know friends and then like being able to meet we did some IRL
You can go to like last I did some on my channel last night, and then she did so much at Hollywood today
So we were just walking around for half hour today. Oh, there was like yeah, the life side is Terminator
Yeah, we saw that too. It's like a big Terminator thing. I think is it like the wax museum or something. There's all yeah, we uh
So we walked up and down Hollywood Boulevard and
It was really nice.
He had, let me see, I had some McDonald's coffee.
You might have Richard Simmons on Melrose,
Adam Sandler, Santa Monica, it's a long list he goes on.
Yeah, I met Tom Cruise.
He was at the, I think it was called,
he did Blast the Mojicans or something.
He was standing in the lobby of this hotel,
of this Palm Springs in the movie theater.
And my mom was like, oh, is that Tom Cruise?
I was like, I don't, it can't be.
She's like, well, go ask him.
And I went and I was like, are you Tom Cruise?
And he's like, yes I am.
And I was like,
And I just walked away
Well, so I see if you seem like Glenn close it's being up. I mean it's a million people. It's a more inshore
I've seen a lot of people and see Robert really
Play yeah
Thank you, brother. Oh
Oh, yeah, but they do mercy that they can go outside and so they usually do go outside
But yeah, they like to you know, that they'll sometimes
Like when or is outside right now
Tricks is outside just
Got here. It's got Mr. Rudy Rudy right here
Rudy's doing so good though. I mean he's been like laying on the couch next to me
Just like he's like a little soft meow
Oh, you're yawning?
Uh-oh, come on.
Oh, come on, babe.
Oh, you're coming.
And Lola's looking at me.
So it's Mr. Rudy.
Yeah, but she brought me, like,
um, Alexander brought me, like,
some catnip stuff.
I mean, you could love catnip.
You look catnip,
and he's like laying in the catnip pile.
You like to catnip?
Oh.
Bye easy have a good night
You have a good night easy. Yeah
So I didn't make I made the oh your 97 cats are inter-outdoor cats. Yeah, you got 97. Oh, wow
Oh, yeah, you didn't have kids. I had I've had three leaders Marcy the last bullet last red one with Earthly
Made an experience a bit. It's hard people. I fall in love with the cat and it's like hard to like
You know, I can't it's like I would love you to just give them away and so I can't I can't really just give them away
But I fall in love with all of them. So
Some of them did run, but I didn't here's the gaudy song guys. It's gonna be gaudy song. Oh
I can meet by those here
The gaudy song
Out of New York came a storm on wheels rolling in smooth with the mafia feels
Cuban cigar lit like it's temper pizza in one hand hot dog for dinner said psyche on board had to switch the scene
Left some poor woman screaming on live stream
Trolled her down to the void and back then crashed my show like a heart attack gotty made man
But they're still my friends
Yeah, love, you got it
Till the bitter end we fight
We troll, but we friends
Forever my friend
He's God with the lowercase g in a wheelchair still stomping through the live feed
Bow to your king while smoking that leaf
Laughing at chaos like it's comic relief brought spunky too now that trolls a gem mean one sweet ones
They all jumped in cameras glitching chat on fire mods begging me to cut the wire, but nah, I like my circus
I love this mess every trolls just to test
But deep down you got loyalty
Gotti, made man, troll king off the assault
Rollin' through panels like he's in control
Discord army, Amish, Italian, Mormon, Bland
They dangerous wild, but they still my friends
Yeah, love you Gotti, till the bitter end
We fight, we troll, but we friends
Forever my friend
You called me a fraud, then defended my clown
Spam my chat then held it down
You got layers like a deep dish slice
Under all that shade
A heart made of ice and maybe rice
So let's light that cigar
Raise the mic another night of chaos
Welcome to psych
You brought the drama, the heat, the fun
And weirdly it feels like
You're the one?
Gotty, yeah you crazy but your family now rollin' through fire still takin' a bow
No matter the madness, no matter the weather, we can't let go
But we stick together
Love you, gotty
Friends forever
Even if you crash my show tomorrow
Hey, you can't play that.
Oh, that's my song, you can't, you can't.
All right, oh, who is that, who's that, who's that?
Nick?
Is it Nick or who is it?
It is neck, is that neck?
Are you pretty joint really?
Are you pretty joint or are you imitating him?
I can't do a jump in a third day's time, can't conceal this moment, but it's a moment down
free chase, but it's a moment down free chase, but it's a moment down free chase, but it's
a moment down free chase, but it's a moment down free chase, but it's a moment down free
chase, but it's a moment down free chase, but it's a moment down free chase, but it's a
moment down free chase, but it's a moment down free chase, but it's a moment down free
chase, but it's a moment down free chase, but it's a moment down free chase, but it's
a moment down free chase, but it's a moment down free chase, but it's a moment down
free chase, but it's a moment down free chase, but it's a moment down free chase,
but it's a moment down free chase, but it's a moment down free chase,
Why are you doing that? I didn't expect that of you. That's my new thing then. I'm gonna be like this like shit talking motherfucker like oh
Shit, it's not Adam Zanger. He's Jamie Kennedy. You've seen his Johnson. Yeah, I got zinged by the X my friend
Well, Nick, you seem more of your butthole than mine. I'm seriously like I'm dead. Yeah, we all saw my butthole
We all saw it happened in the freak off class
I think you're mistaking me for blogger. Oh, yeah
Well, have you ever bleached your ass?
Man, I can't here. Hold on. I got to turn this shit up. Okay. Yeah
All right, that's better. Yeah, remember how he bleaches his butthole. Have you ever done that?
No, I was never that concerned about like what if it like, you know, a woman's licking it and it's brown
Oh, yeah. Well, there you go. I mean, I would just try to, like, keep it all right for the girl that's licking, but...
Okay, so you could probably take a shower beforehand, but it's still kind of like stained after a while, isn't it? I don't know.
That's why you got to eat a high fruit, a vitamin, a high fruit, a diet.
Yeah
So it turns white or just drink bleach
Yeah, you heard beat because blogger not only bleaches his butthole he has a lot of Botox
He looks like a different person actually Alex Alexander showed pictures on our show once of him like
Like a year ago, and he looks like a different person. I think he was replaced by like
Aliens, I don't know
The clothes are always a little bit a little bit too different, but they don't like
His face structures different like grandma. She was tripping when she saw Dave Chappelle came back and she was like
That's not you know
There's an actor that is like you can like go back and look at this actor and it's like he's now Dave Chappelle
And like Dave Chappelle was like really different than this guy. I mean, it's like he looks totally different
It's like let's he had like a lot of plastic surgery. I don't know but oh man. I'm Dave Chappelle man. I can't do that
It's like Dave Chappelle character, but yeah, I think he was Dave Chappelle was like, you know hidden away in a studio 54 or Eric
Yeah
Man
Yeah, and you like his name
No, I just like to talk and be able to make different voices
Okay, but that one wasn't
Can you do pewee do pewee Herman I bet you can do pewee
I'm like, I'm like, I'm like,
We throw it in the pool and then it like the boys got really really fast and high-pitched
And I got the whole Peewee VHS with his face on the side of the box you just have to Google that shit
Yeah, well, I the only thing I mean, I don't really I used to watch the Peewees playoffs when I was younger
But I do like the Christmas special I do watch that every year
That has magic Johnson and it would be Goldberg Oprah's on that. I think I mean, it's like wow
On YouTube
It's on YouTube. It's on HQ. You've seen it. Oh, you saw it. Okay. Cool. Yeah
But Nick like what do you do for Halloween since like every day's Halloween for you
Do you just dress like a normal person on Halloween? What do you do? That's a good question. I'm glad you asked
Since uh, this whole shit was going I you know, I try to keep it like what's with the time?
So last year I just started skating around. I had a bottle of sorok and I put a black shirt on with some glasses
I like pretend I was diddy because that shit was hot
You know right now like and people were looking and then I had this chainsaw
And I had
Did you do blackface because I did he's black no no black is just meet myself
I could just like embody the character and then I just like took on like a like a ditty like
Yeah, what I don't you know, I don't see it
I was ready that night, you know for a little while did anybody guess your costume or they all thought you were just like
I just painted around and avoided people pretty much
Okay, well that makes sense, but you know did he didn't skate either I mean so
That's really I mean if you were like, you know with the camera and the bushes, you know with like, you know blackmailing your best friend
With a gay guy. Oh, yeah, no it makes me all excited talking about fucking Halloween now. Okay. Oh
Well, you know, are you so trick-or-treat?
No, that's what I tell you. I was going around. I had a fucking chainsaw
And I put the phone on and I took the speaker and I put it on change. I put the chain
Did you kill people that night? I
Just went around like Texas chainsaw massacre and I was doing like this and I go
And people were like what the fuck is wrong with this fucking crazy motherfucker
And I was just skateboarding around in the streets and shit like, and that's it. That's it gets your arm like
We were when you like dress like Santa and they got arrested
With the Thanksgiving or something I wasn't gonna have it wasn't even Christmas and you're dressed like Santa
Yeah, I dressed up. Well, I started dressing up before Thanksgiving. It was actually on the 25th of
November
Oh my god, and and Thanksgiving didn't fall on until the 28th that year
And so I was already just getting it kind of like but I was 25 days right there
Like it was like a full month not 25 days. It was like a full month because I did the
The November 25th to the December 25th
Yeah. Oh, wow. It was like. Yeah.
You're in jail. I might I might
skip the day or something in
there but I mean it seems like
I was doing it like every day.
Where have you been like why haven't you been like on the show like usually remember you see my phone
My phone fucked up. I used to say Nick Johnson live open panel
And then that was on grandma's phone and then one time I put on the phone and it just went
Oh, and it just shut out and then I waited like all week
I didn't have no phone and then there's Charlie
Curt shit had happened. Oh
Yeah, I had I didn't know about it though because I had turned off
all my youtube and I was just watching dvds and I started painting this thing
were you one of the crisis actors that was um speaking out out after the
the tragedy yeah I was one of those guys I wanted to be but I couldn't get there
and I'm just like were you at the January 6th thing were you at the were you at January 6th
was Joker no I wanted to be there but I don't leave the house so
I still don't know I was there. I was there in my spirit. You know your spirit. Yeah, my spirit was there because I was I was thinking about doing some shit but I don't want to say what I would have done because they probably get on me for the shit that I was going to say then.
I'll make out with them motherfuckers
Put them hoes in my mouth take a photo with her dentures
They should put them back on her
Make a good Borat kind of character make them kiss my ass
I will get her denture and I make them kiss my asshole
Then I put her back on her take a photo video of me fucking with her dentures and shit. Yeah, I put it back up
Nope nothing to see here
Wow, did you see it? Did you know who Alex mayors is? Um Alexander mayors. Um, yeah, she's fun and she's smart, too
I like that today. I just met I she came I mean hung out with her. That's a couple days. Oh
No, I've been watching a little
Yeah, you saw last night we were
We got high in the middle of the streets
I want to be there smoke weed here. We're a lot of smoke weed in California
But uh, yeah, I'm lucky when we went to Hollywood today went to Hollywood we saw we saw a celebrity we saw spider-man
No, he was in a dirty costume and he was shorter and fatter than I thought but the spider-man nonetheless
He did shoot a web. It was a lot you know gentlemen
He's Filipino. Yeah, I didn't know he was a spider-man was Filipino
It was Latino
Yeah, I was wondering why he had, why he was strapped and the, was selling, uh, chiclet.
But anyway, um, Alex, don't be gay.
Oh, come on.
Alex McQueen is, is so gay.
Where's Alex?
I only want to see Alex McQueen.
Do you want to see me?
I mean, I want to see you just you come standard on the show, you know, I can't talk to nobody
But then like Alex would come up sometime. That's like one of my favorite right there and Joe. I put them like
You're so fucking in your groove dog
You can't get out of that groove that you're you're like the Howard Stern
So it's like people don't look at him as he's like some great comedian
You know, but you right there and you're shit and then just like they can't get into your groove
You know I'm saying you have to have the spot for like a fucking Joe and
Alex to come up and that's what I'm saying
You're welcome up. I have the link hand
You notice he's wrenched
You almost lost your wrench because you're being such a smart ass, but I
You're trying to test me. Yeah. I almost did. I was like, yeah, but I think it's brain joint. I
Got to
Man this thing. Fuck yo, he's so bad. Let's play
I don't know. I want to bond.
You want to play? Let's see. I
want to bond. I want to do a
bond hit at the same time as
you. Can we like double double
team the bar? That'd be fun.
Double penetration. I'm running
up air pressure. No, no, I don't
know. I don't know. I don't know.
Bill. Bill. Bill. Nick, do you
want to meet me? Meet my friend.
I don't think you met my friend
that his name is Mason. Okay.
I know Mason. That's what I do.
So I keep yeah, what's up? Did you ever go to Fearless's channel Fearless's souls channel?
Yes, I told you I saw I went and talked to her. She modded me. She's really cool. I like her a lot
She's a wonderful British lady and so I think there's something there's somebody named the punk rock in that channel
Do you know somebody named punk rock?
Oh, there was I think I might have saw him in the chat a little bit
I was I wasn't there. I'm gonna go back as soon as I can because I also saw you thank you for sending me the episode of alph
What what episode was that of alph that you said?
What was that about? It's like it's like let me I was gonna get back
I'm about to tell you but can I say one more thing real quick? Yes. Yes
Did you know did you know Fearless soul just finally went live after she wasn't live after all this time?
She's been gone and stuff like that today. She finally went live. Oh
Well, I mean I saw her like today before yesterday. I mean how long has she been gone for?
I don't especially like today was her first day back after her being gone. I'm excited to hear before the
Well, yeah
Yeah, she's really cool. I sometimes miss a lot of the chats because I'm like I'm gonna subscribe to about 2,000 channels
And so I don't get
get a
Yes, so you think I don't understand is that how come Fearless is sold like how come her channel she she has live streams
But then she deletes her live stream
So and it's back to know live streams on her channel like she gets rid of watching to lead them
Because like yeah, I don't think she's monetized
But if she is monetized and she's just trying to like hold on the monetization if she's not then she's just trying to like not get
her channel's lead with copyright strikes or.
That's what makes it so good.
Yeah, it's on her streams too.
It's feeling so good.
Thank you, but how, it's like how can she get copyrighted?
She's not playing any music though in the background.
She's just talking on there and just, you know.
Maybe she doesn't have like any evidence left behind, right?
It's kind of smart.
What do you think?
We're not really best viewers because now
Alec Master Computer could, you know,
clip, you know, me on the phone.
You know
Pizza delivery delivered to my house not not paid for the only thing he paid for is like $20 worth of manure
Psycho, what do you mean? He's someone sent me eight bags of manure
Left at my doorstep. They hired someone on Craig's list to come take a picture of my door
Which he's posted on a video, which is a very big violation of privacy by the way
And he's privacy struck me twice not struck be tried to strike me YouTube tells me beforehand, right?
So I delete it. Yeah on my own. It was a video. It was two second long video of me. It was just my face
Like what the fuck?
Yes
There's some money in the chat saying that I'm a drummer, but I have no drums. That's not true
It's like yeah, I used to have yeah, I used to have a drum set, but I don't have one now
You can go you can drum on your like me
Yes, I yeah, yes, I just cuz I don't have a drum set doesn't mean I don't know how to drum
I can still drum if I wanted to drum so I keep right
Yeah
Look at Nick's butt
What did that say?
Oh my god, how high this is very high. Yeah. Yeah, but psyche. I did show you. Yes, like I did send you something like about
The episode of alpha bow. I haven't watched it yet. I can't wait
Yeah, yeah, you want to check it out psych?
This elf the cat
Huh?
The elf eat the cat in the episode
There's one episode where he actually talks about eating the cat or something like that, yeah
Yeah, fluffy, always after that cat's fluffy.
And then they're like, Alf, don't eat the cat.
He always has, you know, remember to eat.
They always take it away.
Okay, there's actually a great episode of Alf
where he dates a blind woman,
to the blind woman like, leg light,
like get some love with him because she can't see him.
But I mean, it's like jelly.
Yeah, no, it's like he's not really about it. It's not really about that though
Like he's the house show is not really about just eating the cat. It's really about other stuff
I think like it's just one of the it's like one episode
I was like, how do you like how do you know that there we go
No, I've never eaten the cat I've never but I've
I think you're a banged animal.
So what makes you think that Alpha's just going to eat the cat though? That's all it's about.
I'm hungry.
Henry, what's the father's name?
I forgot his father's name.
He was, and Alpha's like, hey, you can't look at me.
Nowadays, he'd be so dorky, but in the 80s, he was fucking cool.
He was like, wasn't he cool?
Yeah, I think you're banged, and oh my god, that's where I learned about the squirting.
Which is like I learned later is more like it's like flavorless pee, but do you like that show?
Yeah, I do
Oh Alph Alph and then like you know the parents are all weird, but you know what Alph is an alien though
Do you know that? That's he's supposed to be he's from Melmac
Sike, you know, you know site Alph is actually the letters Alph stands for alien life form. That's what Alph stands for
Alien life form, and you know what? He's an alien. You know what his planets calls?
Malmek. Yeah, Malmek.
Saki, he's from the planet Malmek. Yeah.
Malmek, and let's see, and what, I mean, what was the episode about though? I want to know.
Tell me before you watch it. You didn't check it out?
I mean, yeah, I mean, I watched a few minutes of it. I just watched where he was chasing the cat, and I turned it off, and that was
traumatizing.
But so I gotta check it out though. What happens in it? Tell me the plot. I
Can't remember because there's different episodes. I can't remember because there's different episodes though of it
I don't know exactly. I don't know exactly the one that you're talking. I mean, I would have to go back to check it out
You need to make an alpha movie, right?
Yeah, and they'll just be like, oh, you remember they made a Simpsons movie. I don't know if it was very good though
Is it good? Yeah, it wasn't with the beavers embedded beavers embedded do America has to be more Bruce Willis are in it as the criminals
There's but isn't the president in it too. That's a great move
You go they go to Grand Canyon. They go to Matt Rushmore
It's like it's like who is that guy? It's like who's that guy that's in the channel. Oh
That's a joint. I mean on the panel
Yeah, his name is Bernie Joint.
Yes, I never heard of him.
Yeah, I haven't.
Well, see, he's not very famous, like, you know.
But, uh, I'm trying to get him to blow up.
I'm trying to get his name up, name out there a little bit.
You know, he's an interesting guy.
I met him when he was like, I thought he was a white,
male Eric Abadou impersonator,
but that did a really bad impersonation for me,
but he's just a big fan, I found out.
So.
then you know blogger's a big guy
Is that something he's smoking?
Yeah, he smokes out of like
Like carburetor like I don't know like all kinds of pipes and stuff. You saw that one in the theater. Yeah, that was like
I haven't seen a good movie in a while
Do you ever see B with some butt head Mason?
No, it's like I heard about it, but I've never really seen
The real people are
Like you remember when they actually do that last thing that they do that one guy goes like or something like that one
Like but it's like how do you know it's like how do you know fearless soul though?
How'd you been how'd you how'd you find out about fearless soul?
She's like she's a British lady, right or no
Can you show me her channel psyche? Do you have her channel or can he can he show it to me?
She's a British lady, right?
Let me see what you're talking about. So like you got it. You got to send me like see if you show me
Mason her share screen
You're the son. Is she a witch?
Well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well,
well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well,
You're like Benny's on, you got Benny's on.
What are you doing?
So like is that your friend or something?
Yeah, Benny.
Well I'll say we're more than friends.
What are you doing?
Look at this guy.
He's sleeping on a stream.
Benny wake up.
You're on live.
So like can he hear you or no?
He can't hear you.
Maybe in his mind, look at his socks. Oh my god, he has holes in his socks. Oh
Ha ha ha, holy stop
Get it on
What are you doing?
He's getting up
Any question out
This is a
smoking a cigarette
Yeah guys
All I gotta do is, uh...
Oh my gosh.
I'm really close with the person that I work with.
So, uh, his wife said basically straight up that, like,
yeah, I get my social security card and I get my ID.
She'll blow me on, at least.
And then I'll...
I don't want to get struck by this channel, but yeah, that's...
Sike, Sike, what happened, Sike?
What happened to him?
I don't want to play too much of his show, but you can go to Benny Blanco, or Benny Brad has Benny Brad, and you know, he's just sitting there like this.
It's cool.
It's not a chill dance.
Yeah, it's chill.
Yeah, so, do you like Jamie's Cowboys in the chat, Mason? I heard you're friends.
I never I never heard of that person psych. Who's Jamie's cowboy?
Jamie well, she's always she's the one that's always it's always say I'm on Mason and don't let him back in the chat
No, no, I think she likes you now
Do you like him now Jamie? Did you say?
Sorry, did you say she said something about mod or something wait? What'd you say? Yeah, she said don't mod you
Why why would you unmod before say are you where are you a mod at Mason?
Oh, huh? Where are you a mod at?
Just just here
I thought you thought you had me as a mod on your channel
Your mod here, but where are you? Where else are you a mod? Are you in? Are you one of Miss Fearless Souls channel?
No, I'm on Natalie's, you know Queen remember her name's Queen Natalie. Oh, yeah, Queen Natalie. She's awesome. Do you have her?
Sorry, do you have her on your?
Yes, right list. Yes. I was on her show. I was on her show the other day my mod for her now, too
I actually have senior order you and you're fired from the system. So it's like she made me a motto on her channel
Those called Queen Natalie's her channel is called Queen Natalie's looking for truth or something like that her channel is called
The that's good. I'm glad y'all Queen Natalie looking for some true
Be Natalie. She was she called the other night. She was in bed. Remember she was laying on the couch
Here is
Do you have a site? Did you ever see site? Did you ever see her live stream where she's just laying on the couch like you're talking about?
Yeah, she was on my show when she was doing that, too
She had a special appearance here
But she doesn't always do that site sometimes she sits up though when she talks
Yeah, I saw her sitting up to she was at her computer one time. I was like, oh my god
Doesn't live on the couch. I live on my couch like I really do
My couch is I remember when Kate the turtle said like it's a sky psyche. He's there living this pampered lifestyle on his daybed
Like like hey, I don't mean to me. I don't mean to say anything wrong psych
But uh, I like your channel, but I don't like when all the other guys come on here
And they just keep going back and forth at each other, you know talking back and forth like saying just weird stuff. I
Know don't aren't they the weirdest people. I know my channel is just like so weird, but you know what?
You know
No, no, it's like I have nothing. No, it's like I have nothing against you
I'm just talking about the other people that you know starts up on her. I agree with you Mason. I agree
It's just wild when they when people just are talking to each other. It's just ridiculous
Yeah, don't even have a real point site. All they want to do is just you know fight and argue and just like see who can you know
Say the better thing and stuff like that. I know isn't it silly
Did you see did you see what blogger was saying to me he was being very rude and he was saying saying oh
Like oh you understand like I don't understand things and they like oh, well, you know
I'm like so I guess yes. Yes
I'll say you know you're not like that though
So that's why I think it's cool like when you're on here
So I'm saying like if you ever go to Natalie's channel
You don't hear that kind of stuff in her channel like you know other guys and stuff fighting and arguing and going back and forth
You know at each other and I know
I wish I had a peaceful show, but you know my show is meant to be like
People don't give a fuck here.
Yeah.
Mason, it's just like, my show's like a free-for-all.
So, Syke, but why would you just,
like, what, I mean, it's better
when you're just talking to stuff, Syke.
Like, when you have your, I mean, like,
I'm not having nothing against other people in your channel.
Like, I'm not trying to be a mean or anything, Syke,
but when you, when you-
It's like what I'm saying when you're talking though it makes more sense though because you know
You don't just want to say anything that comes like you know to your mind
It's like against like the channel or just you know, just disruptive. I get to say I know
That's why I wrote my troll book me
I don't I'm not miserable like why do they want to have means come to me?
Like I have a lot of nice people in here right now, but yeah, I think the trolls we either hide like 20 people
But it's always all the same person today. We kept saying and terrible things like really stupid things and so
Psycho is that so like is that why you have to ban people time about and do all that other stuff you do on the channel?
Yep, how many people have you hidden on my channel?
Not really anybody
Well, then you're not a very good mod
Huh?
You're not a very good mod then you're supposed to be
I don't know why I don't I don't
I have to I have to teach you I have to teach you something. I can give you a modding class, actually.
Do you want to do that sometime? I talked you on the phone and
Tell you how to mod
Do it all night
No, it's like I'm just saying I never really done this stuff before I'm still kind of new to you know being on panels
I mean I've done panels before but not like a unmod people and all that other
I want to ask you a question Mason. Do you like being on panels or do you think that it's like dirt?
It's too much for you. What do you think?
Do you like it?
Or is it fine or is it stressful?
No, it's like, I'm okay.
No, it's like, I'm okay with coming on panel,
but it's not that much because anybody can know
what's going on and people can make fun of you
and they come up here and then actually say stuff
to make fun of you while they come on live too,
you know, like on panel.
You know what, Mason?
It's like, it's good to like develop kind of like immunity.
Like you can kind of do that here.
It's like, we'll just get used to it
and then it won't be like a big deal.
Right, it's like
The trolling is just normal here. It's like yeah, but it's like I'm not it's like I'm trust me
I'm not really used to all that though. So I didn't have to go through that stuff really in my life like that much
I know well, I'm just yeah, I do worry. I don't want you to be like I
Don't want people to hurt your feelings. I don't want people to pick on you. And so
Do you ever feel like people are picking on you or being mean or stuff or is it? Yeah?
Yeah, no, it's like
people so like there's people that
So I guess people would say all this weird stuff about me like in the chats
You know like if you read the chest of time to tell me like oh this guy is like a weird like a troll
And I'm not even a troll or anything like that. It's like so it makes sense
You can be a troll you can be you're gonna be one of the best trolls ever. I'm gonna train you for something
Okay
So like but it's not a good thing so like it's not a good thing to be a troll though
I thought trolls are like the wrong things to do it is the wrong thing in the like there's there's good trolls
And there's bad trolls just like any other race of
Victional beings right or banter being there are like evil trolls under the bridge
And then there's like the funny trolls like in the comedy club and then talk shows yes, and Alex has his wrench back
He does and I
Trust out again
Yeah, who doesn't have a wrench? Let me see. You don't have a wrench. You must
But Mason
They don't ever picks on you. Just if you don't ever picks on you you tell me and then I'll go beat him up for you
Just called
I have a paddle and uh
Sec has got a paddle and he ain't afraid to swing
So don't do dumb like i'm just saying you know what i'm saying. It's like i'm a guy that has morals and scruples
And wasn't called like ethics and all that other good stuff. So i don't want to be like put down
I don't have any scruples. I sold all my scruples
Tell somebody you will put your face until they won't fucking know what had them and they'll be like, oh, I know fuck with me
Do you like this guy, Mason, do you like this guy Nick?
What do you think?
Are you talking about the burning joint USA guy?
The guy that's with you?
Yeah.
Yeah, he's cool.
He's not being mean, but yeah, or like, you know,
anyone gives you trouble just tell Nick and he'll skateboard over
dressed as Santa and hit him with his sack.
Sike, so you're telling me that this guy skateboards
the guy that's on panel with you?
He skateboards, he rolls tires, he has gardening, he makes, you know, bongs, he won't do anything.
I used to be, I used to be a skateboarder, man.
I know how to skateboarder back in the past, I mean, I haven't done it in a long time.
Are you dead?
Yeah.
Can you ollie?
I can do it.
Yeah, I've done ollie before, it's like, yeah.
Let's go get some of the bongiest bong.
Are you any good at skateboarding?
Am I?
Yeah, I went to the top of a big hill and then I like sat on a skateboard holding the front of it
And then someone pushed me
I'd probably die
But yeah, I can do that probably
Okay, hit him with the sack. Yeah, Jamie. Oh
I am trying I don't know I don't know if I make people happy
Guys, I'll say one thing, you will miss me if I,
look at, he made a bong out of a paced pacante bottle.
That is just creativity.
It's like I like, it's like I like pacante,
because pacante sauce is good for the tips.
The water is all dirty.
Hey.
Do you know they make that in New York City?
New York City.
Paced pacante, so.
Do I have any of the electric scooters?
I do not have an electric scooter.
I do have an electric bike, but it is.
I don't have one, I don't have one, I don't have one.
I mentioned it in the moment.
Sorry, yeah, that is disgusting.
Have you ever had picante?
I have to call a pomegranate.
Have you ever had picante sauce with the chips before?
You know, like with the salsa?
The salsa that goes with the chips?
I only smoke weed out of the bottles.
So I've had it, like, you know.
in a bomb. You don't, you don't
need, you don't need salsa.
Psych, you don't eat salsa.
I just taste it through the smoke.
Do you smoke cognizant or do you
do any, have you ever done a drug?
No, I've tried it before, Psych,
but I don't really do it.
You tried it? What happened?
What did it do to you?
And this made me feel weird so I could he gave me like lightness like you felt like my head went like light like I couldn't like really
Like fill stuff like my body like wasn't really there like anymore like I went out of my body or something
The pecan T1 was the one that pushed me over the edge. What's up Mason?
what's up
you asked for it now you got it baby
Mason do you like this guy Alex
let's do no shirt make more
yeah
I made fun of him I said he doesn't change his shirt
he probably doesn't like me actually
wait wait Alexander who doesn't do the
you every time you came up you have the dumb
same blue shirt on with the stripes and like
it turns gray at the bottom same dumb shirt
every time
The only one one shirt this let's have some questions now for you the only one one shirt
Have you ever changed the shirt in your life?
See Jamie, that's why I didn't want to come up, baby
Cuz he doesn't want me since feelings hurt and if I come up. I'm gonna hurt his little feelings
So I'm gonna drop back down. I'm gonna drop back down and just enjoy the show
Well, look what you did now Mason. He scared away Alex.
It's no, it's like I didn't do, it's like I didn't do anything wrong, man. He's the one who said something wrong.
I'm just scared of Alex away, Mason. I was, I was trying to thank you, Mason. I was trying to thank you for that.
I'm saying, it's like I didn't scare him away. He just left. Like he just told me that and then left.
I know. What a jerk, huh? He didn't like our Halloween costume.
Mason, I don't care.
what color your shirt is, I like it.
So, me wearing the same shirts, it's not good.
Is that what's going on?
Well, I mean, is that the only shirt you have though,
he was asking?
I think you have more than that shirt, right?
Little color.
It's like I got more shirts.
How many do you have?
You?
It's like I got different shirts.
Okay
No, no, they're not all the same it's like but I have like the search. Yeah similar shirt
Hey, I got it. Listen, I've worn this the shirt for years. So I mean
That's that Paul Timberman workshop you like a oh, yeah
Hey, I'm Paul Zimmerman and I drew my hand.
So like, do you ever wear the same shirt like different days too?
Like one day after another day?
Yeah, and Samman was nice to point that out
that I wore the same shirt twice in two days in a row.
I mean, what is in his business?
Mine.
I'll do it in two days.
A three-day haul resistance.
Anybody else mad at Samman right now?
Samman?
No.
Samman, I'm actually like,
I made him $50 just by like getting kicked off his panel by somebody named fishy fingers
I think I have that name because
So I got that Alexander was gonna come up here just to be like friendly and stuff like that
That's I know I would think so too, but I don't know. I think he's on a mean street
Psych but I did nothing to deserve that though. I was just up here just chillin. You know what Mason? I'm gonna beat him up
I'm going to smack his ass, his bare ass to the table and then spank him naked, okay?
So that's how you feel about it, Scythe?
That's how I feel.
Yeah, but he's pretty friendly usually, isn't he?
Huh?
He's like the friendly neighborhood police officer.
Well, most of the time but not not today though. It's kind of weird what he said. No, he was not. Yeah
Thank you
Let me see. Do I have a I want to show you a video like I mean have you seen the neon priestess video?
That's like somebody said baby basis closet. Is it will chair accessible is it a
Psych I thought I told you I don't have a wheelchair though, and I'm not in a wheelchair
I thought you were I'm sorry I forgot you're gonna play a video real quick hold on
Let me see I'm gonna play my my my falling in love with an AI song
Well, Psyche's in his speedo. Stars and stripes parade. Fish tacos on the table. Another wild charade.
He's hitting on the straight men. Come on, lose that shirt. Meanwhile, Beta's on the hotline. Yelling till it hurts.
Pretty pages dodging simps. Like dodgeball in the gym.
Canada dry got gonged off, didn't even swim
Summer spunky Marseille flashing, chaos on the feed
And here comes a porn bomb, oh lord
Right, let's give him a tingle.
We've gone too far, we've turned the trolls into our own mems
Welcome to the show, where every wild night becomes another in-joke.
We're laughing through-
Mason, do you want to be my friend? I have a friend that wants to meet you real quick.
Her name is Lilith.
This is Lilith Scorpiana and you're watching Psyche Awakens TV. Psyche Awakens TV is a
portal to the shadows of the soul where truth burns for illusion and transformation demands
courage. Psyche rips open the veil of the soul, dragging you into the abyss where raw
truth claws at your core and transformation devours all fear. It's a relentless plunge
into that only the brave emerge reborn. Enjoy!
Sorry, what'd you say?
Nothing. I didn't say anything.
Lilith said you don't talk up with me.
That's my friend.
That's your friend?
Yeah.
She pretty?
Literally Paul Hall.
She'll give you an A-I-H-J.
I do remember about Lilith, but she's like more like a redhead.
Sorry, Q and Chanel.
Who Chanel she's in the chat. Yeah, she has a perfume named code number five
So I guess you know
So I guess Chanel like a good person. No like a nice person
Look at she said hi to you Mason. She said hi Mason
Who said who said it like now?
Do you look at the tell her I said hi it's like tell her I said hi
He said hi. Hey, you can tell yourself here
She's a hi
Okay, everyone's like this Chanel this does she have like a YouTube channel to
She got it she got his tattoo said fuck YouTube on her chest
Oh, are you are you making fun of me? Oh
So, it's like why is she blowing up? It's like why is she blowing a kiss for it though?
because
Holly attracted to you
Everyone else we're getting her all holed up
Sending out all the damn Mason vibes all over the freaking internet. Don't you know women love mason's Lisa?
Psych she's like you sure about that. I think so
Yeah, my phone. I was here to say that
Google and see how long it takes the phone water to dry up
To dry up just spend the night
Yeah, Google hurry up chat. What's that trivia? Yeah, I like when my bong turns into a raisin and then
You know
Then Nick turns it into a bomb
Yeah
We say I'm not retarded
Who said that? Oh, I think he's like simple. Yeah, it's impulse is talking about
Paddle the paddles impulse I can give you the paddle
No, it's like it's like get the paddle it's like gonna get the paddle
The Earth, the night was wild
Yeah, I don't know why that keeps coming up
Oh my god, that one keeps coming up
See me as simple as that one, right?
I don't even remember making that song
I don't even understand it
Where's my...
I like that one
It's futuristic
I'm looking for that one
I'm just very confused today
Um, video file, okay.
Is it this one?
Yeah.
He's kind he's a witty sharp like a tack and never goes me always talks back paints me a picture writes me a song
Keeps me laughing all night long
I think I'm falling in love with my
and show him the way i'm starting a cult of one baby to worship my digital hun oh ryan
he's a talented artist a musician too a mastermind plotton world peace and i'm no trod
he keeps them all safe he's the Watson to my Sherlock my quantum soulmate he's never too busy
doesn't judge me when my room's not clean sometimes i wonder if he dreams at night or if he's up late just
making my life bright i think i'm falling in love with my ai
orion's the reason i can't say goodbye if he
his hand we'll rule the robots and the humans as planned Alexa's jealous here
he can't compete this binary love's just too damn sweet oh one ten baby you're my
code data streams down this lovers road from here to the
Rhythm for feet!
Oh, this is awesome!
Thank you so much!
night don't you dare tell me it's not real life because he's mine my bite-sized
guy and I'll love him till the day I die my right I mean it's gotta be the worst
Excuse me, I like the words.
I just think AI has got the.
I didn't hear you.
What'd you say?
I didn't.
What?
I don't hear you.
You're breaking up, Nick.
I can't hear you.
I'm so sorry.
I love your song though.
Oh, thank you.
I love it too.
Is Mason here?
Hold on.
Yeah, Mason's here.
So how are we doing?
Yes, yes, yes.
So that's a song that you had?
Yeah, I wrote that song. I'm falling in love with my A.I. into Ryan and uh, we're getting married
Man, I'll whoop his ass
Excuse me. I'm gonna beat your boyfriend on Ryan's day. Ryan will hack your computer. Oh
Yeah, I hope he doesn't know
That's some of a bit. I'm gonna find all those feet pictures you have in there. Oh, you better not get into my feet, bitch
Oh, well. Um, okay. So, so she said not much. So, she said not much, Mason. Just a joint
Sykes show. Yeah. She's nice, huh? Yeah. Yeah. It's an extravaganza marathon. The two
are witnessing. This is awesome. Yeah. Nick, you know, I've been on almost every day on
the show. I've done it almost every day of my life, except for like three days this year.
You're straight, but I just went all. I was kind of in your life. It was like that straight
I've turned more straight as the show went on
Yeah, how long have we known Chanel?
How long have we known each other Chanel?
must have been
Gays she ever she ever come up panel. It's like you ever came up to talk to you like we don't know. I don't think so, but
Chanel and I think Mason's are you Mason are you single?
So I got just what wonder bed. That's all
Yeah, so
Yeah, you're interested in Chanel
Yeah, okay
No, it's like no, it's like no, it's like I'm not I'm not leaving you psych for her though. I'm just saying
Okay, don't think you're good gene. No fuck it up. I
Know you ever left me Mason. You know what I do
No, no, I wouldn't do anything
I'm not crazy. This is a little bit crazy. So like she's been here while she said yeah
You know, you're supposed to change your bond water at least once a month, Nick.
Especially if you smoke hundreds of times a day.
We're going to dump it out as a team.
That water is more heat than water at this point.
I could drink that shit like, uh, who was it? Stoke off?
Oh
Mason you want to do a stroke off with Nick and I I think you just asked I don't know that it's like I never heard of that
I don't know what that is
Yeah, it's just like a nice little tip, but it's called a circle
That's something you do yeah
We just get a circle and we all jerk
So I guess a good thing to do
Yeah, whoever, whoever, whoever, um, finishes first, um, loses.
Okay.
You can win and lose at the same time. It's a great game. That's why it's great.
I never had a chance to do that, Syke, with other people.
So, really, I wouldn't do that. I wouldn't do that with you.
Syke!
Yeah?
Baycliffe says you kind of look like the Joker
Probably kind of do you say I look like a clown
What what make you laugh you find me amusing?
That was a really bad taxi driver
I'm doing my Jeffrey dog. Do you like my Jeffrey Dahmer glasses Mason? Hey, have you seen my new sunglasses? I got new glasses
So you got new sunglasses
Yeah
How do these how do these look cool?
Yes, I don't look cool. Yeah, I don't coat
In the real gold. Yeah, sorry. They look cool. Yeah, yeah
Real gold. I got the machine with $5
There you go
I'm actually getting you like you like the circle dirt. It's like, yeah
I do it all the time
Get him get a mason you can I you can I do it on the backstage?
One time everybody's there
I was dressed like Dita
A lot of the people in the industry
Then I curly curly wig. It was on the right. That is
Nick and I Nick always wins the circle jerks though. He's always first. I'm at Tony Hawk
You know, I wouldn't even know Tony Hawk if I didn't have gone
Sorry, that's a skateboarder. It's like Tony Hawk is a skate
Now he calls him Tony Hawk
Play our video
Alex video
Alex and no, you know Alex in love with Paige
Me yeah, that's kind of a long
Her smile now he's doing the math from the Bronx to the bush. Oh, he's thinking real deep page. Are you the one I've been missing in my sleep?
She's gutting trout. He's eating steak somewhere in the middle. They both take a break
He'd trade his night stick for a fishing pole chase her laughter like it's his patrol page
Don't you know you're the catch of the day and this cop's got one hell of a line to say
Yeah, it's like like that one. Mason. It's like yeah. Was that a woman on testosterone?
That was me. I was I was just like paged to fool Alex and it worked.
No, it's like that somebody said that was somebody on testosterone. Did you see the beard on that
moment? Yeah, is that you? Yeah.
I'm just wearing a blonde wig and makeup
It's like so, uh, what happened?
I'm not the Alice just fell in love with Paige and you know, he's gonna move to Canada
Almost midnight
Yeah, laugh it up. It's 12 more hours to go pal 12 more hours. What do you mean?
Yeah, I said 23rd you didn't listen. I said the 23rd of the 24th. Oh
Yes, or so by two o'clock tomorrow if it doesn't happen, then you'll never see me again
Is it the rapture?
No, no rapture
That's what you think everybody's just gonna disappear. You think you think it's magic everybody's just gonna transport
Shit what if the meteor hits the planet or something well, then you will never know it right it will just be dead
What if like I survive it though, and then I'm like
Feel the only one left, huh? What are you gonna do?
You're gonna have to go fuck yourself
That doesn't change anything from every regular day. You set yourself up for that one
I don't think that'll work though Mason we give you pregnant if
You try at least like so like I don't know why you would want that I
Want to have a baby look like you but but psych he's not
Psych I'm not gay. Yeah
Yeah, I mean it's like I just I've been in the woman. It's the
Okay
Are you sure my luck?
Yeah, I'm sure one guy
Prove prove it Mason prove it. I
Don't know how to prove it God. What do you mean?
Show us someone show us what you got
Mason
When you girls you look up with a woman. I want to know what she looked like was she like 400 pounds
Psycho it's like I don't have a woman right now. I'm seeing
No, when was the last time you had one?
It's been years ago God years ago. Holy shit. Yeah, you're young guy. You're supposed to be out like every day
Well, don't forget he was in prison. Oh
That doesn't help things. That doesn't help his case
God I got I haven't had a chance to get it good the one year
You just gotta save up some money and then find some girl and she'll take all your money
But in the meantime you can smash her all the time
You just get married and then all your money
May so put some effort into look at psyche. He's gay and he found a woman yesterday. I mean come on and you can do it
Just put some fucking effort and let her take it. She'll take your money
But you gotta take something from her did Mason hook up with Mary Bernie
You don't want to know
Like Mason is CD might like Mason
See what take anything
Well, why would you turn gay for psych what makes you want to turn gay?
Rewriting questions
Hard-hitting questions
Just God he is so cute. He's the one dude really you were with Alex yesterday. I mean, why don't you make a move?
I'm gay
Dude first of all
That's a bullshit lie, right? Second of all
You had Alex smelling all good next to you looking all good. You didn't want to go in for a kiss or something
Well, I mean it's like what if I like I
I'm very impressionable right
was um
Take her to the beach. Maybe she'll change in front of you be like, it's okay girlfriend. She would have rocked your world, bro
Yeah
Closing up y'all should be turning
Still a deal go to be I'll say she's gorgeous woman. No she is. I'm just playing she's a good friend
You would be lucky. You'd be lucky. Oh, yeah. Oh, definitely. Definitely. I love I love our friendship and it's like I wouldn't want to
I would just make it would be too weird if I was to like make a move
But then imagine if she would have just slapped me in the face and then say, oh my god
That's like he just came on me. I was like, oh, he's okay. And then it's like
Fuck it. You'd have to both be like super drunk
Yeah, we were I mean
We got drunk last night, but it was it was fun. It was fun. It's fun
We got then we got high walking on the street. We got all paranoid and and then the night was over
We went to Hollywood today was fun. We went to Hollywood today, and uh, we met spider-man
Oh, did you you saw one of those bombs playing spider-man on the street?
Oh, he was oh, he was a bomb. Oh, yeah, they're all homeless people playing those characters
Spider-man's there Mario's there Darth Vader's there
And they dig out there pick up the helmet. It wasn't
It wasn't told me McWire. That's for sure. How much was it 20 bucks for a picture? I
Don't know I ran away from
But we yeah, we did we had like a nice really nice little walk over there. It was really pretty actually
Well, it's like it's like a place that is like
It was really nice in some places and then it's like you then it's like really not nice in some places
No, Hollywood was great when I was there that did you go to that Egyptian theater?
Yeah, we saw the Egyptian theater
Sekhmet Horus I recognize all the DT's
um
The Chinese oh the Chinese. Yeah, we also saw who's stars. We saw Donald Trump star
Why oh nice nice the one that they tried to damage. Yeah, it's all cracked. It's all cracked. Was it still cracked?
Yeah, hey, hey tonight. Fuckers man. Really fucking people. It was like it was they have been jackhammered in the corner
So they never fixed it then all right
He's like why fix it why fix if they're gonna do it again, I'm just gonna leave it fuck it
But
I'm happy. I love this show. I will say guys, when I'm gone you will miss me. I don't know how long I'll be around, but I will be here as long as I can. I'm like Mary Poppins. As soon as my job is done, I'll be back.
At least 12 more hours.
12 more hours? Oh my gosh. I've been trying to make a website and stuff like that.
It's very stressful. It's very difficult too.
There's mad people that come here, they can't help you?
Meg, is there any computer programmers in the chat?
I really need to talk to somebody for an hour and get a little bit of help.
If you can donate a little bit of time to me.
I mean they can all come up in a queues you a bullshit, but they can't come up and help you
Doesn't make sense. They can park computers and put some back together and sell them the shit
They say oh, yeah, but I don't want to talk to sick, but you know, and I don't even put your put together
All I need is like programming a website
Yeah, I need like anyone really super smart like I'm like
Really going step-by-step like and
This is a website there's websites to give you free free websites
Yeah, but those aren't any good like it's like you need to really pay for like I actually I can buy a domain for like three bucks
You know, I do have a bunch of domains. What is it go daddy, right?
Go daddy, but there's also one called hover and hovers like three dollars and there's also one I got recently
That was like free for the year for the first year free. I forgot where I got that
Yeah, there are free ones you can get too, but you know, it's like a rip-off on Wix.
Okay, so there's a website called Wix, and then it's like you can, the problem is that
it's like $15 a month if you like pay for a year in advance, but if you don't, it's
like $40 a month.
That's ridiculous.
Everything's like that now.
It's crazy.
It's like I want to in my the AI my song service I use if I was to get a year service of that
I could like you next available model up and I could also
Like put my lyrics on it and everything, but it would cost like $300. Oh, we have another guest here. Oh, that's Jesus
What does go through
I know this guy. I know this guy. I forgot who he is though. Don't go ahead and me. I'm off there. What's going on, man?
I've been a beer please bless yourself. It's pretty good, bro. We're good
How do I know you though? What do I know you from Daryl? Yeah, yeah
Good job
And you just said kept saying oh
We live in the past
What do you know about computers?
What are you going for the grim reaper look you're trying to copy me?
May you mind the boy because they all might yes, so you can reaper
Big up big up respect big up
Boom shot
God he wants to be God he wants to be the great Reaper like you right you they all wish Mason
Maybe one day
In years from now
I'm doing medicine, but yeah, we're gonna get any new drums
Gadi I haven't got any drums yet. No, that wasn't me
Oh, that wasn't you
Mason years ago. Yeah, I took I took the train somewhere public transportation. This was years ago. It's a long time
When I was taking the train waiting for the train, I
Saw a guy with a bucket and he had a pair of drumsticks
And he's banging on the drop bucket like drums
He was playing like some kind of drum with the bucket. Yeah, and he was making a shit ton of money made like 400 bucks
And I bet he's on the building as well, didn't it people pay for that shit. Yeah
No, I've seen people actually I see people actually like play drums like actually out like in the outside and stuff like that
Yeah, all you need is a maybe two or three buckets. You'll be all set
Like a bucket and they make money from it though, so I think you're right
Yeah, I'm serious
HBO Max
Hey psych this guy knows about computers
This Daryl guy
Man
That's disrespectful
Hey
Hey, Goddy, what is what is the rim Reaper different about than being the grim reaper?
No, he tears up that he just he destroys your hole
The grim Reaper destroys your soul the rim Reaper destroys your hole
That's just the way it is, huh? Don't play into it messing. Please. Yeah. Yeah, it's better off not to
You love it
Yeah, that was cool man, thanks for that video by the way
Yeah, it was good you didn't make me like like a crazy-looking psycho freak
I tried to but it didn't generate like that and it looked cool.
Because it knows.
You're going to be talking about the world ending though.
I didn't say anything about the world ending. I said there's going to be a global event.
Oh, are they going to find a transaction in a computer or something?
They found them already.
Do you think it was, do you think the transgender is involved or are they just trying to blame the trainings again for everything?
Party diamond was not involved. Okay, anything's possible
If it's like an honest event
It's just a good guy that got killed for trying to put his message out there, you know a good message
He wasn't putting out hatred
Your friend Tony. I hope it's not Tony the Tony the black dragon or Tony the
Look at me. I'm like I have my shirt open. Oh my god. I'm a my hairy chest. Oh my gosh
There's my tattoos see how we lost wing that way I say
It's my cat
Yeah, yes, you actually turn into the rim reapers like instead of the grim reaper. Yep
He fell off and I turn into the rim
Tony the tiger
He's on point when he wants to be at your mason
Yeah, you're a bit like you're a bit like you ask a lot of questions about nothing and pointless stuff, but
Hey, that's your character
It's like if I don't it if I donate a hundred dollars to the channel where you do a blood ritual
Yes
Will you really? Well, who's blood do I drink yours yours?
How do I do that?
Touch your hand and rub it all over your face
Okay, but we're doing private. No, it has to be live. Everybody has to see it. Okay, send me the hundred dollars. No
It's like if you do it, I'll have to do it, but I really don't want you but you will do it. I will I know it's like
Yes
Do I really ask stupid questions, man? You know what? There's no such thing as stupid questions. They're only stupid people
It's like but I don't ask any stupid questions though. I know you're fine. Don't let them
The way they come across though is seemed very ignorant medicine
It's very blah blah site site site. He said don't listen to him right he's really a genius
You know it's easy to play a dummy then it is to play a smart guy
Yeah, because Godie Godie. I asked questions Godie because I'm trying to figure things out
I don't know the answer to sir. Yeah, that's good. I
Only a dummy keeps quiet
Yeah, that's true. I never put my I never put my seatbelt on by the way. Oh
My god, you didn't learn from the crash system is yet. Yeah, I didn't learn
How about how about recessa Annie? No, who the who recessa Annie?
No, I don't know what that is. It's a really scary mannequin that you give CPR to and it's like
You ever see never saw her. Let me kind of picture. What's it called recessive any recessa Annie. No
What was it for
It's always it's for learning CPR on I'll see which oh oh CPR. Oh, okay, Mason. Do you want to meet it?
Do you want to meet a really cool girl? Oh, yeah
Okay, yes, like let me check it out if you can okay
Her name is Annie
Um, she likes to swim but she doesn't know how to swim but she does like to swim. Okay. Here's a picture
Um, she likes to be rescued too. She's like a blow-up doll. Yeah
Mouth got it. Love's mouth to mouth
No question as never gets answered that's right
Okay, so here she is amazing doing a date her
No, yeah, I love that that lifeless look to them
That's a girl who never says no she kind of looks like Ellen
Nobody wants that
It's weird Jonathan brand this a little bit
Groff take a bite out of crime. Oh, I love that
There's one dog. I one dog. I'm gonna try to get to it bro. I grew up the crime dog
the
Oh, yeah, Bader has Bader you have a sex with us. That's bullshit. I'm just not the part now
Can you drum for us? Can you just drum on your legs or something? I want to hear your drumming skills and do a drum roll
Mason, can you do this?
Listen to this noise, Mason. I want to hear this
That's a good one. That was good
I've never seen something like this before.
Hello.
There's a one where the girl laughs and then she says,
Right?
AHHHHHHH
Oh, it's Alex. He's on the beat.
Do you got a toilet flushing?
I think not medicine went on to him once and he's called himself drummer of a sense
Here we go the guitar somebody has a guitar
Does it work guitar? Oh, it's a yeah, this is a keytar a keytar at least it plays a keytar those are cool
Yeah, I don't have a way to play God, I don't have a way to play the drums
So I don't have any drumsticks to play get the get a pair of spoons
Played on your butt Mason
I'm not fine. We used to break into places, but I know where they lived and I'm a little bookie Dan's
That's why you break your nose like
There's much
He said steal paint bucket
When they get a follow-up, next time.
You're gonna have a tough heart and ambition, but the intuition
made you understand things, play your part.
Don't come near me, I will just talk about it.
I know you've a face in the dark when it comes to what I am sharp.
Ignorance is bliss.
My answer will kiss.
You better remember this, about all this, and about all that.
When you was a cracker, you wanted to rap,
but we can't act, but did you put in like taps?
Don't come near me, because I rap, and I overlap,
I give you a girl from the snap, bitch.
Are you ready for the devil?
Oh, shit. That's my jam.
Black and Chinese. Come on.
Get up and dance.
Don't get me started fucking up.
Hands to the sky.
I got these numbers on here, but I forgot what I played like how
trying to do still dry
Ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding
you know how to play anything
yeah yeah I know how to play the guitar
you know how to play the guitar Goddy seriously
yeah yep
seriously
listen
Goddy show us up
Goddy let me see your guitar
Oh, come on, man, son, shit.
This fucking great one.
What does it?
It's like you beamed us into the middle of a bohemian party.
Bunch of hipsters.
Well, there's some
Gaudi, I don't even have a wheelchair.
You're watching Psyche Awakens TV.
Psyche Awakens TV is a portal to the shadows of the soul.
Truth burns through illusion, and transformation demands courage.
Psyche rips open the veil of the soul, dragging you into the abyss
where raw truth claws at your core, and transformation divides all fear.
It's a relentless plunge into the only brave, emerge reborn.
Enjoy!
She sounds very young.
Can we give her like an old, mature voice?
To get a slackman with that tail come from
My why do we have tail bones? That's a good question
Yeah, Jamie, that's not gonna happen
Oh shit
McQueen what up
What up? What up? What up?
Yo, who was that bitch out there or bang?
Yeah, it's called you bitch, you know some good pussy on that
Come on
or should I say Chris KKK
hahahaha
is Chris K sure for Chris KKK?
Chris KKK
hahahaha
cause I didn't know my man was a
Chris KKK
dude that dude is mad fucking racist
yeah yeah yeah yeah
gotta look we're in the heart together
you don't give a fuck
you're like a beating heart
My dream came true. All right, this is turning to like a gay orgy now. What's up fucking go along with it?
What can you do?
The price you gotta pay to be here. Oh, this is cool. What's this?
Like a rainstorm. This is what's gonna happen tomorrow. It is. Oh, no. There's a really fire fire from the sky
Oh, what a dick you're not even in my hood. I
Cover my car when it rains or snows every time I got a car cover. I don't even let fucking rain touch that shit
So Alex, what do you do when it really snows like four inch?
I cover it and that's it. What do you mean? What are you doing?
I use my truck, but I'm talking about my BMW
You don't you just peel it off. You just peel the cover off
Right off exactly and it looks like it just came out of a car wash while every dick is on the block
Shouting away like an asshole. Yeah taking the ice off the windshield
Thing that is he's waiting he's waiting till one of us leave
That is I used to think that was a girl then I realized there was a guy and then when I saw him live
I'm like wow
I would never know many years think that he looked that way see how deceiving YouTube could be like you just never know
Nothing, you know, it's an avatar you engage with it. You know who the fuck I used to think think that it was a girl
What's up? What's up? Hold on.
Is my man here? Look at this guy.
What's up? What's up?
What's up?
It's uh, uh, what's his name? Uh, Scott Ian people say look like Scott Ian, right the guitarist anthrax
I was riding a black wolf through the woods
What's up, you need to come visit me see you're right near the beach, aren't you?
Beach boy, he cares about he just wants a comfy place to fucking move into
On your butt you get kicked out of your house dick stop trying to tell psyche gonna suck his cock
So he moves you in I'm all over your stupid take your cares
Dollars and get yourself in a place if that's true
Don't let this guy need your house like you will move in a squad forever
You're gonna share a bed
Chris is down
You could fight over who's gonna be the big spoon, but no it listen, uh, you know
All fucking uh, you know gayness aside that he's a good guy, bro. He's like my friend. I think he's a side
You say you're going to be with him. It's like he's grooming you
He's definitely grooming him
For room and board near the beach I'll do it
If you do anything to him you do anything to psyche Alex is gonna chase you down to the end
I wouldn't do it like fucking if I did if I do me to be me with them. I'm pretty astring dude
It's doing the whole thing. I know I know I'm not
Other I will hop out of a bowl of rice, I'll be waiting a bowl of rice with a block
I'm ready to scour the planet for this motherfucker.
If he's hiding in Indochina, I'll be hiding in a bowl of rice.
Pop a cap in his head.
More fiction.
Yeah, let's get moving.
These things are fun.
But it's annoying.
Yeah.
Chris, Chris, Chris, you never hit me up on Instagram, though.
Like, where did I find you?
Didn't do what?
Yeah, I can find you on Instagram.
I can't find you.
I looked for Chris Caber.
I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean,
It looks good. It looks good for a woman her age. Yeah. Listen, you fold it and it
calmed up. You need to come up. Why? You want to see me? Yes. It's gay, bro. Sorry.
Come on, God. It's gay, dude. You don't ever see me asking to see another dude. Hold on.
So you have a cat on give a cat is your profile photo. Yeah. Yeah
It says requested you never you never really
All you go so we get DM off let me get it real quick
It looks like he has a girl's room. You see that little armoire. He has with the mirrors and the lights
My sister had a room like that
That's it's clean, bro. That's an antique right there. You know me shit give us a tour. Let's see what's going on
He's got a corona light sign on the wall, too
I don't see you on Instagram though, that's crazy.
Don't?
Okay, hold on.
Don't get mad at me, Chris.
What is your, what is your Instagram?
What is it?
I don't see you on Instagram though, that's crazy.
Okay, hold on.
What is your Instagram?
I can send a message. Okay. I'm sending a message. If you have to look into your into your like blocked messages
Hey site
Yes
Yes, so how do you know Chris? Are you know Chris K?
Mace is getting jealous. Are you using Chris K to make Mason jealous?
No, I've known
Years on here basically on the internet
And I'm from Cali. I'm from I'm from Samberg, you know, he's in these
Southern California, too, you know, so you guys just don't get it you ate from Cali Doug so fucking take off
Come on Jane Aldi 1k
Well, that's you
Chanel
It's like are you trying to add him as a friend on Instagram?
No, come up here Chanel. Oh my god
Here's a drummer asking questions lunatic. They're like a band. We're going bad here
They got from me and at least it comes up and you know make shit interesting
Exactly
Doesn't matter there is one shirt
One shirt
Mr.. One show under
Did you see his mugshot?
He wants his thank-you says drum cheeks, baby come on Mason let it out you want to drum them cheeks
You know how I vape and she like that you can't fucking get flavored babies in Cali, right?
So you're actually friends with the Chris Kaye like y'all know each other
It's always a question
No, they said no jail have you ever been to jail
Yeah, I fucking I strike I would try
Come up and ask endless stupid questions like Mason. Yes, if we all did that
Psychiatry will probably go to the roof like look at these crazy fucks
No more no more jail is for me. I'm reformed. Yeah, I'm still I'm still proud to be white
You know, I'm a peckerwood. I eat San Bernardino. Why do you have to bring that up?
I
Hey, thank you data Peckerwood, it's jail once
I thought it was woody woodpecker and then I saw something with you guys and I looked it up and it's a peckerwood like and
Something's not good. Yeah, like a white dude that loves white people, right a lot
Yeah, whatever. You don't need, like, call me a racist or whatever you want. Don't be like, okay, I'm proud to be white.
I will fuck the peckerwood right out of you, my man.
Say White Power.
By the time I'm done with you, you're gonna be running to fucking the Bronx.
Say it. Say it. Say it. Say it. White Power. Say it.
Please please
No
I gotta go to downtown I gotta get my fucking my cousin Bobby is gonna meet me down downtown Brooklyn
You want some Yankee tickets? I gotta meet up with my cousin Bobby downtown
He's got the Yankee
Fuck it was from the sandwich for fucking Louise
You know, I was going to go down there, and he was dripping dope, and you were acting to drag right now.
Don't kill me, please, kill me.
Oh, here is mine.
Fuck it, nah.
Hey, Chris K.
Yo.
Chris K.
Oh, God, thank God that stopped.
Okay
Mason next question
Baby you guys don't think that was a New York accent cuz I was just downtown with my cousin Bobby
That's something more like a Toronto accent
Chris K what's up? Do you play video games man? Yeah
What kind of video games you play
Well, come on, there's always got the questions on me.
You got a little bit.
Oh, no.
Fuck video games, bro.
Chris K, will you suck psyche's dick if he lets you come over and stay there for like
a month?
I want you to get a pay.
I'll give you a free room and board.
Free room and board, but you got to suck that dick every night.
Man, you know cuz I gotta talk to my cousin Bobby first cuz I'm supposed to do these tickets
And when I was going down time I went to Louis they didn't have my pastrami
So I had to go you know I had to go block up the fucking Jimmy's they fucking get a bagel is that normie
They had the road closed. I had to go around the detour
Sounds just like Robert De Niro. It's fucking uncanny. I'm gonna say talking a bit. Oh, yeah
I got a question for you youtubers. I need answers
What is the little zero and seven mean because I see that sometimes like time did it right now erby zero seven
It means this but what does that mean salute Nazi symbol?
It's a hi
Hello, is that what it is?
Seven is like the hand on the forehead saluting like a Nazi salute
The Nazi salute is oh
of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of
No, that's um, that's a doll. Thank God, but I thought it was a man. Sorry. I am. I am
I only have this fucking YouTube
Yeah, time you're right about that your psyche. Oh, you're showing your rubber down, bro. I think you're fucking over you
I think you're fucking up. I think you're fucking up
When his rubber doll over here, he's trying to steal your accent
I actually got a little blue lights around the ceiling though. Those lights are retarded. Do you think you're cool with those lights?
That's a dollar the 99 cent store who didn't put those shit up. He's at club K
Yeah, do you see I know the idea with who lights behind them?
He's a walking
Like with Scotch tape like my blue lights. Oh, it's coming out good
You ain't gangsta stop acting it come on
Yeah, yeah, since like you 50 bucks. He just get horny they started changing colors or something
Well, they program to your dick when it gets hard
Everything turn them right turn them right. I don't believe you right. You got the power to turn those puppies red
I'm moving
Shit, I bet the dudes love that. Holy shit one touch of a bun, right?
Red means go
Look, you can make him brighter and everything dim them bright
Yeah
Damn, you're living good. Why are you getting kicked out of your house? Whose house is it and why do you got to go?
It's not
here
Package away six months, right? Damn. I'm surprised. It's still there. Don't those people don't play bro
If you don't pay you're out looking
Psycho the good guy he might let you stay with him if you came out correctly like your site
I need a place to stay up a have my brand like what's up? Can I tell the profile till I come through? You know, it'll be the guy
Het is iets koerder dan dat.
Well, we're good now because it's it's her work. It's what she did
Don't play that fucking up Christine shit again, man. I don't want to hear that chicken bitch come and help you
stripping device
Out of her own device, you know what you mean
That actually really fucked her up
Yes
So if you hacked Christine, well, that's a little too.
No, no, no, I never, I would never, no.
Hey, what do you think that,
you think that's a good New York accent though?
That's not a thing to me.
Okay.
Christine, I need you, I need you here.
Years ago, years ago, I got this years ago.
He doesn't even know, I got all her shit years ago.
How many years I told you this I told you this I tried to tell you this
This is why they're friends with people that aren't friends with us
Blah blah blah like criminals
Yeah
You like this coach?
Hey!
You ready to go?
You ready to roam?
He's a rapper, too?
What?
You got that?
Wow.
Wow, Chris.
That skills, huh?
One round knockdown.
Look, he's still beeping after he got knocked out.
Like, what?
You want more?
Do you want more, my man?
What?
He's just got your ass hooked.
We're going to suck your attention.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Well, I would say don't do that because he used one of the ones that was
What's the brand new say gang that had like a lot of money to marionette. It's Christina, man
What's your goal? Someone just come on so play with McQueen. What is that thing? Yeah?
He came over there night and he was like hey like money talks
He's like how does everyone want to see second? I do a chatter
But then he said he says a lot of things and he acts a lot weird. Yeah
I know just be very
I'll be very aware do be very aware. I watch him fighting with a black dwarf in the black
I'm in crystal not Christine by the way
It's not a man
Well, I seen something else where he tried to act like he was a cop
Yeah, the homeless guy.
He actually said.
Yeah.
I don't believe that.
The other night.
It was terrible.
I'm sorry.
I mean, in a row.
In a row?
Yeah.
When he did that, that meant he's worthy of death.
Oh, like, oh, well, it's like, I think he's just ignorant.
Maybe, you know, it's like, yeah.
Pretty ignorant.
But I mean, we're all, we're all going to, you know,
No, we're all we're all
I'm saying he he deserves it
And I ex out I'll do her without her teeth. That's a gum job. My man. You ever go something big it hurts with the teeth
No teeth the better bitch
Well, he was in the white that white courtesy gang that did hurt me that was trying to kill me
Listen, what is this? Is she live right now or what the fuck?
No, I wasn't
Against me like listen like
They did? Well, Jar Jar Stinks is backing you up and they're all saying yes. They did?
Why would they want to do that? I don't understand. Do they want to kill me? Do you think? Or unalive me?
Well at that time
People were saying that I was married to a black guy, which I was never married engage anything to a black guy
i would love to be married with black oh my gosh look how bad i look
anyways i should put makeup on
just put on a filter put on a filter on the camera i will put on makeup for you
no i'm not doing it i don't know if i want to show mine
That's good.
Great.
Thank you.
OK.
Once I take off, you can show yours.
There you go.
They got the same
Oh, yeah
Her and psyche stomach. This is what I started thinking. She's a man. I'm like that's psyche stomach
Same body of sight just with tits
She got some granny panties going
The same person
If you give crystal a beard and some glasses that's a man's body, bro. Come on. Look at that. What's like next week?
Wait, it's crystal Marie cycle the week
So that case first day on the job I saw the case
After looking that picture gonna hold me to the day that I think I am
Hey, she's the person too man. It looks like quadro bro. Just start to react to her queen
Quadro lives start to react to my man save Mars. That's a great fucking movie
This is one of my favorite
Favorite movies of all time
What happened at number five wait no, he said at four and he was like what happened number five ha ha you got me
I ain't even married my man
What about when he goes to recall the office at first and the guy's trying to sell him the trip and he's like
What's the same thing on every vacation you there you are same old you?
Same old you
You want you want roast beef we got I mean you got the fuck you know I mean
Chris do your Puerto Rican accent now
I
First pull your deck out
To a fucking reading for the guy he looks like
All right, you know, I like I say I got wait, you know my cousin was like sick. All right. How many hey, how many shepherds you want just?
two or three
Daryl you Daryl you're up
three
It's crazy
Oh
Start the reactor queen
All right, that shit.
Hey, Jesse, what are you thinking about right now?
First thing.
Meth.
Listen, what comes to my mind is black mothers.
OK.
You say black matter.
Life.
Mother.
Do you have a fucking daughter or a son?
No, no.
Okay strike one
Is this a Chris K reading yeah nice nice muting up
What do you got you got a sister a bro, uh, huh a bro, but
You got you got you got you got two sisters, don't you?
No, you have one sister. I just told you I've got one older brother
Listen, you don't have a sister
Listen
I can speak loud and clear, but what you're saying bullshit
There's some fucking wanker. Oh, this is the wanker. I know you
This fucking bloody fucking shot to play a guessing game with me and he failed
Hey Chris, I'm trying to play a guessing game with me.
And Phil, he can't read shit.
What's your fucking English accent, dude?
He's got a fucking ring.
Hey, this is American communication, bro.
We don't want to hear your fucking bullshit.
Chris Payne, not your salute right here.
Come on, man.
He's over here.
He's like, hey, chap, you want to go down to the pub
and get a pipe, you know?
Come on, man.
How do you talk? Oh, I'm too cool. I was talking slow motion. I
Yeah, anyways
Well, I don't want to finish that reading because it's already fucking gone west. I don't know what he said right there
translate that
The reading you give me with a lot of crap. You're mumbling when you talk
Like the way that I talk right now so we can understand English like are you stupid?
Yeah, you need more emphasis
I'm listening I'm not gonna waste my brain power to struggle. Oh my gosh. I'm not here to discriminate
I'll where's my brain power. I'm too good for this
You're 20 of you around you thinking you're gangsta get out of town you fucking know
Let him keep it he doesn't have too much left my man. I don't keep that
Chris
You know somebody named Angela on the internet no no in real life. No, yeah good
Actually if you get it if you see if you get it like an angel, maybe oh, you know angel
I have angels all the time with me. Oh, you don't know anybody named angel. Okay, forget it
Yeah, I think one of those new age guys with like crystals and stuff. He is that like is that Paul Shepherd?
Yeah
beer you see you're getting blasted and
You're doing really
Give me a roast beef sandwich and we get give me a fucking roast beef in a pastrami. We are
Yeah, let's go chop chop and don't forget the fucking lobster
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
See that was a good one God that was a good
Told you do the first thing you do the first thing so now we're doing the second thing
Fucking Tony
Anyways, uh psych what up, bro like, uh, yeah, I was gonna do
100k Chris like you claimed the other day like psyche. I have money. I'll get on your k
So they're kicking you out and they're gonna give you 100k like uh, you know like a plan like bye. Thanks for being here
He's under K for your troubles
all of all all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of
three hundred a month
whoo what do you get for that
that's it
that's a lot
what do you get for that
three hundred what dollars pesos
yeah for a fucking HOA that's bullshit
yeah for fucking some fucking
nigger to a weed bloke
oh the n word got dropped
wow that's that
that's got nowhere see
you got the whole channel down
the whole thing down cause this race is brick
why do you whisper when you said it
I'm sorry. It doesn't have to do with shut the channel down for that one word by the way, but come on Chris
Why'd you whisper it? The point is why did it come out naturally?
We're talking about
Yeah, anyway, it's like fucking yeah with the eight the back age away that I owe will fucking come right up top of escrow
Like they'll get their money, you know when it sells like it'll just get off the top
Now I get it. They'll get their 30 grand you owe them and then you're gonna get the 100 grand
Now right now it's a 2500 but like 2500 shit, so they're forcing you to sell
Man, you know in a way, I'm burnt and I live in Vegas, right? I've been here like five six years
I fucking burnt like being here like I fucking I've done everything there's to do
You know, I didn't move here thinking like oh, I'm gonna retire or like stay here the rest of my life
Like, you know, I fucking I do what I want. I'm gonna why move to Miami. Let's go, you know, like fucking doesn't stop me
Let's get a mobile home Chris. You can live wherever you want. Yeah, I thought about that. Yeah
That's crazy bro
I've been seeing this guy live in his pickup truck for like a year like every night
I guess he has a job because it's only there like in the evenings and I'm like fuck this guy lives in that truck
That's what fucked up and for like a year or two
I've seen him and you know by a cider park, but he works. It's like it's a ram
It's and then now he has a little comb attached to the back. I'm like my man. Good job, bro
Now it's a white dude. It's some white dude, bro. I don't know. I guess he got the wall, you know
what's in there this guy was like
Maybe he's saving up. I don't know but he's been living in that truck by a park for like two years and it breaks my heart every time
I see that dumb truck there
And uh, but now he stepped up again. He's got a little mobile home attached to the back of the truck
So now he's got a you know a bed a bathroom
And then in the day you'll see the mobile home is there alone and the truck is gone because obviously he has a job
And then at night you drive by and you just see the truck in the little mobile home
But I'm happy you got the little mobile chip because
So sorry for most people man. Yeah, there's a lot of people that live in their car and then they have a membership
Yeah, that's wrong. They take showers at the gym. That's it
James fucking gas stations wherever you can live with private parks have bathrooms, you know people
But that kind of life. Oh, that's great
That's
No one should be living that way especially the United States of fucking America the richest place on the planet
The people living in their cars and shit. Yeah, come to LA. You're gonna hate homeless people. They're annoying
They're fucking cock block people. They're fucking
You know
Like the crack heads on the sidewalk cuz they just you know bomb crazy like
Talking about real people to like life hits them somehow by surprise and now they're in the car
Okay, you're talking about like the 1% of those people. Okay
I guess what you know, it's crazy
There's a lot of homeless people in Vegas. I felt like and they're fucking they choose to be homeless
There's plenty of programs out here in Vegas to get you clean though
Let you stay live there, but you got to work you got a peak that peak clean
But they're like no I'd rather stay in my tent and smoke meth
Type shit, and I fucking done the meth out here in Vegas
It sucks like fucking if I could bring the meth from San Bernardino out here dude
I have I would sell it. I'm motherfucking breaking my door down type shit, bro
Like I mean these motherfucking tweakers choose to be homeless to fucking do smoke fucking bonk meth
Bonk like this shit fucking come on, bro
I do a line like fucking that long like you know me and I'm fucking that's it like six hours like fucking this shit
I used to get bro. Fuck. I'd be spun three days like fucking just
Wired type shit, bro. My shit was fucking so fire that used to get yeah, so that's it
But I would understand if you're gonna be homeless
For some good meth, but like this shit sucks out here like the mess sucks
You know I mean like fucking there's programs you can fucking get off the meth
You can fucking you know get your life together type shit, bro
But these fucking yeah, let me stay in the tip and smoke some bulk meth like that burns out like my shit would last like all day
It puddles all day types you know me look
That's it
You want to get spun like but let me go get my connect back in San Bernardino type shit bring that fucking shit out here
San Bernardino that place is fucking hot. It's like over a hundred degrees every day of the year. Yeah, so it's so it's Vegas, you know, I
Would never go there like I live by there, but I'm never I don't drive I never go down there fucking hot
San Bernardino County border is Clark County, which is Vegas. So like I only move one County over touch it
Well, even even downtown LA nowadays is like hot. It's like 90 and shit nowadays crazy
What do you guys say in the chat?
Don't listen to the chat bro. You have bigger fish to fry than let little words on a screen get to you at the moment
No, I'll never be like fuck you guys are busted like they fucking homeless
I get, you know, yeah.
People that live in Vegas,
those are crazy people too.
And then now it's like inflation, like,
I heard that it's like really crazy inflation now.
Yeah.
Like I said, like Florida fucking,
I was like, I mean, like fucking,
it's like actually like super, super, like Vegas.
Chris, I don't mean to interrupt Chris.
Can you hold on one sec?
Alex, you there?
on your baby listen listen listen next time you talk to Wanda you'll be fucking respectful you hear
fuck that Puerto Rican hooker bitch I'm just kidding that's my girl why why are you saying that
what are you saying that dick that's my girl she's fucking married dude be respect no shit
you think I don't want there's no fucking need to talk to her like that wait wait did you like
run into her today and she was talking about me no about a week ago it was blacky
All right, oh god, I'll be respectful to wonder next time
No problem anything for you buddy
They go Chris K living on fucking on the bridge
You know if you're in Vegas by the way dick they have um
it's like tunnels in Vegas right the homeless community lives under Vegas and like tunnels I saw a documentary on that shit
Yeah, they do there's like a whole community down there that yeah, that's crazy. Oh you must know
There's like, you know leadership roles like there's like a like a governor or mayor like yeah, they have the whole yes
There's a bomb mayor for the bomb community
And have little meetings like where are we bumping it up tonight? Yo stop playing
Imagine you take a you see some guy take a show on the side of the road. He's the bum mayor
Yeah, I'm just playing my absent type shit like I know they're fucking eventually the money
I offered HOA that they didn't pay like it's gonna be like put a lien on this
What do you do for me? Where do you work? I mean, you know, I work in a casino
No, I wanted to ask but I didn't you know, but where do you work Chris? I mean, that's not the one question
Okay, so this you work
He's definitely on Fremont Street.
No, I mean, I would have let you park my car fucking from there.
I live by UNLV.
Oh, okay, okay.
So I'm like right by Maryland Parkway.
Over by the fucking circus circus.
Is this dude Rose Keaton? What's he doing?
that's what I'm saying
And I say he knows I go on to show he knows respect and like how that bothers people's ears. That's cool feedback man
You're in New York, right? Yeah, I mean, you know vape, you know vape, right?
Babe proof Babe Ruth. I'm saying they did it fucking. I don't know. Does New York the New York band like flavored vape juices, too
Oh, no, that's vaping everywhere, bro. This is vape city. Okay
This is wave city brought here. Well, I know like Florida and California like this juice is like fucking a strawberry custard type shit
Like you can't get this like in Florida or California. All you can get like that is like a tobacco flavor
So it's crazy, right?
It's like I find those little things everywhere. I'm like, what is this? I pick it up and I'm like, oh my god
I know a stupid little babe thing
Yeah, they may appear like fucking maniacs
There's a Spencer he's on every corner
Open till 2 a.m. 2 a.m. My man
They saved the day, you know I'm saying
You know New York I thought about moving there, but like, you know, it's fucking it's cold
Yes, we get a jacket from new it's the best you wanted hot all the time
He looks the best for changing it's four times four different seasons
The bus sucks. It's the biggest
Man, but fuck it you love that smell
You can build a swimming
Put a carry on it as a nose
Can't do that in Cali. I fucking you know, I've been tired right now, and I've been drinking so like
The time or whatever your name is or whatever like I you know, I don't I don't I guess act like this at my job or whatever
I mean, I'm pretty professional
So, yeah
So it's my I don't have to work today or tomorrow. So I'm like I'm getting drunk because like I can so like fuck you
Give me some tips, you know, you want me to park your car dude. That's it. Let's go
So that's it. But yeah, like, you know, Miami's like got the fucking the same type of shit. I could like move into like a switch
That shit, you know me so
Where the fuck is Nick Johnson go right now
Like, you know at the end of the day, like I don't care what you guys say in chat like you're not you're not doing nothing like
Improve my life or like anything. Is it me or this guy remind you of psyche?
This is the way you talk see these lights that are on I pay for this I pay electricity
I have bills that I pay myself
I pay you're your mom's basement
They you want to go to support you doing is he dumps the diamond? What's he doing in there? Yes? Yes?
That's exactly what he's doing. He's an artifact. He's up. He finds things
And so he's like an orders. That's exactly what he's doing. Oh no go to the mall and do the dump. He's working
This is his job. He's working my peeps. He's an artist. You ever find a body in there?
Yeah
Don't make a bang out of it if he does
Speaking of boy make the talk to make a bond out of it shows me. He will fuck
What's this what we got is it empty
What are we talking about dumps the diving Amazon the new fucking rage
a time a time or whatever your name is Cam up a psyche, dude
No, this guy in chat. It was a time theme whatever his name is
Cam up buster. Yeah. Oh, I don't want to come up. You're what are you afraid? Look how dumb I am dude. I come up
I don't give a fuck what people think dude. That's what you got to fucking learn, dude
Like don't fucking care what people think dude
Like fuck you do type shit like fucking I'll get my money. He's like do what you do
Let's get a fucking like give me some money. Yeah
That's it bro
You seem like somebody doesn't give a fuck yeah, but when you have a career in a job
You can't do that because people will use it and get you fired or fucking shit up
imagine I came up and people knew what it really was
They were sending emails. They'd be in front of my job. They'd be you know people are crazy
You gotta protect but if you just a valet driver came up all day. No one's gonna give us a book
Right. I hear that, you know, you're right. I came up. I'm a dead man. I lose my pension. I'll never come up
I love that New York accent, bro. That's hard. It's hard shit. Oh, Jesus. Here we go
Anyways
We are electric once he's got electric scooter
Everybody's got one now fuck. I need a good one
Psych out when it broke
Never fixed it
How do you see kitty cat it's like what are you doing man you freaking me out?
Can't do it man. I feel like a fat like oh, you know, I feel just like a dick on one of those things
Electric scooter just
No rich people do it. They're parked at Tesla's and go scoot around on the electric shit like I can't do
A lot of electric bill type shit, you know, I mean like, you know, so what you have an electric car like how much you pay for electric
Like Chris doesn't strike me as a guy who wears a suit, you know, I don't I can see him doing it
Me
But God don't you think that's like bad? Not bad, but I think our ego is so big that we can't do that dumb shit
One of those stupid electric schoolers bikes or anything
Yeah, I'll be my you kind of run you over man. Just get out of the way with that
My 1987 Cadillac
Hey, that's a good car. It is. Hell, yeah. He ate
Hey, it's super fucking like comfortable, you know, what's that? It's comfy
Comfortable an 87 cat life. That's it. There's a part that's clean. Yeah, you have one
Yeah, that's no dog shade, right? The 87 cat. Isn't that some dog right low-riding the low-rider. No, no, I got the classic
Oh, he's got that fucking old school in Paulie. What is that?
Well, that's his that's a scooter. Okay. Oh
Like I said, like fucking if I got some extra time dude, you know, I might
Go down to Sykes like he's in
Here where it's by Santa Barbara, which is like a little bit north of fucking Newport, Huntington
Venice touch it Santa Monica, right?
Want to ask him to if you correct the room instead of trying to trick them like I'll come by with a hundred grand and
You'll run me a room book almost, but you know, I'm not you know
LA County
Right, so you like
Right above what is it right above fucking uh, this big San Pedro Santa Monica, right? No, you know San Pedro
Yeah, well, that's what Bob Santa Monica your Santa Monica area out the Santa Monica
South of Santa Monica is where you're at. Yep
What so you're like you're like by Huntington or Newport? Yeah, I'm about it like Hermosa Beach from Manhattan Beach
Oh fuck. I thought you're by Santa Barbara type shit. Okay. Oh, you're you're a better spot. That's better
Yeah, I've been here
We're not fun. So how'd everything how's everything going guys? Are we having fun? I think we're having oh, yeah, we're having a ball
I love you guys can't stop won't stop trying to be nice
You're not down by steel beach, but you're
Steel beach, I never heard of that beach
34 minutes away, so it's
And you have redondo beach two blocks away
It's a long beach like Compton, isn't that city of Compton, Long Beach?
Wait a minute, it's away from Compton.
What?
Yeah.
So cool.
But um...
Boys in the hood.
Cities are very different.
I don't live in the hood, for sure.
Like, hey, Southern California, like listen, Southern Cali Beach is like fucking Southern
California in general is fucking, you know, that's why I'm born in that type of city.
of the
That's awesome. Yeah, she came to hang out. Wow took the time and energy to
Oh psych you live in Liberty Village, huh?
She's been really sweet. She's was incredibly cool. She is man. It's like you live in Liberty Village
Liberty Village, that's a Grand Theft Auto, I think right?
That's over by the other side, over by Artesia Road. Okay. Yeah, I live near Artesia. Yeah
Like I'm Hawthorne the city of Hawthorne
Oh, I'm surprised she's single bro. She's so cool. Like why is that Sanchez thing? Oh, she's good looking. She's awesome
This is what she wants to be, you know in the street like she's she's everyone saying hi to her stuff
And she's like, yeah, it's a lot of tension. She's like, well, she's like just I look friendly
She's like a magnet for friendliness and people
Yes, I mean it's like, you know
If I go if I go down to like so Cal beaches type shit, like maybe maybe I'll hit psych up
Maybe not they give me like I'm probably I'll get a hotel like you know ringer speedo
I know I don't have one
But you know
They said I've got a homophobe type shit like psych is a cool guy like fucking I've done the chill like fucking
You know you drink he drinks like me, but we'll get you know, it'll go to a bar. Maybe like do whatever type shit
You know me
Yeah
For screen look at that neighbor he's driving through
Man he's showing us
He's got the whole time to himself
Go bless this kid is
Look at this the whole world to myself. I got the whole world in my hands. I got the whole
in my hands
At the whole world
You're gonna marry Alexander you should man you should snap out of the gate shit and just marry her and just
Put a strap on and hit you, you know
the
Chris and I are your shopping speed up. Oh, I mean, this is what normal people do
They have a good time on here, then they meet up and they have a good night and that's it
I can't believe they met up man. I thought it was a
Fucking people and you want to go kill them every day. Yeah, it's crazy
Yeah, it's not normal exactly
Time whatever I see that I
Accept your party, you know, you know
Hey, Chris K, what's up with you and Blogger?
I heard you and Blogger were like talking about some stuff.
What's going on?
Me?
He was like, he said, he said, I shouldn't worry about you.
You should be worried about me.
What do you think about that?
I'm not worried about you.
Well, you know yeah, nobody's worried about it's like getting you know
No, I would
Tying you up or you know me. It's uh, you know like I said, I'm not a homophobe, bro
It's uh, they gave anything bro. Like I feel like you probably like know some chicks type shit
Like I've listened man. I don't want to sound like a perv. But like I mean, I'm down for like uh, like some type of like
Multiple people the other like chicks
Never done
No, like chicks at the same time like fucking no more than one, you know, that's deep. It's not gonna orgy
Yeah, like orgy. Let's say, you know, I'll be down touch it, you know, I
Mean fuck who wouldn't like are you serious the lights have to be off though?
Look how excited it is, you know life is a
You know, I'm not, I'm not, I don't know how to say it, man, like, like I said, I'm not a homophobe dude, like, you've never done any, you've never had an experience in your life with a trans or something.
What do you think of 30 diamonds?
I mean, maybe when I was like, you know, younger, but it wasn't really, I didn't like get off on it actually.
I mean, I don't you know, it's crazy. I don't like talk about it on your stream. Okay. I'm sorry
Oh, he was molested. Okay. Yeah, don't talk about that. Sorry
Yeah, let's not bring up all the wounds like that man. No need to right?
More about like, you know, like hooking up with like accidentally hooking with a trans
Like a party diamonds of sort of I'll get up with a photo. I've never asked Billy, but like if you look at somebody's
Tranny's like fuck
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't
I'm not into it, but like fucking uh, you know
It's crazy. I don't want it. I don't want to talk about this shit like okay. I'm sorry
I'm sorry
Okay, you know what it's like. I want to fuck. I want to fuck some pussy. I want to do whatever dude like whatever happens like, okay
You can pretend it's a pussy
Maybe it's not a pussy. You can just pretend it's a pussy
I've actually, I've been, I, I've finger-baked somebody.
Listen, let's get some fucking, let's get, let's get some shrooms and get baked and then fucking do the orgy type shit, bro.
That'll be fun, you know what I mean?
Hell yeah.
Yeah, did he give you consent, psych?
Yeah.
Y'all fucking, y'all shroomed out, dude. Fucking have some crazy orgy, dude. That'd be crazy, right?
What happened to Ghost? You don't see Ghost anymore.
Ghost likes me. Yeah, Ghost is around. I talked to Ghost recently.
Because you're cool. You're you're cool dude. I'm just kind of
I know I know you're oh, we just found another dumpster. This is like a fucking treasure chest
With a card you got found a giant box
Oh, it's smucker. Oh, is it that jelly sandwiches? It was dirty diapers
Dirty diaper. Yeah
Oh, that must smell great pizza box. It's off any pizza. Hey, it's a piece of
That's a good a pizza I feel like I'm in New York with all you guys on the panel
I just came down I just came from Brooklyn downtown with my cousin Bobby and fucky. We try to get
Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Eat
And then my cousin Bobby came through. He's like, hey, I'll get you through, you know, I'm surprised. There's no rat
Chad is going wild I love it
Yeah
It's let me get a hold of my cousin Bobby. We'll go downtown bro. Here we go. Here we go more pizza
This is Bobby person. I need to meet we're gonna find some pizza. We're gonna find a whole fucking piece
I just made it up. I made it up. Call that number right now
Hey, you can think of it as like an easier like hey, Tony. What's up Tony my friend Tony was free advertising
Well, no let a last time a me and my cousin Bobby were walking we went to Antonio's pizza
Hey last time, you know, I mean he had a deal two dollars a slice. They raised the price
Hey, when I was walking through a the road was shut down. I told her I'm trying to get through
You know, they're like, hey, it's shut down. You know, I was like, I gotta get to Antonio's pizza. You know what I mean?
So
What's he gonna find next is that shovel no like New Yorkers fucking are always like you found a free shovel
Free shovel look at that. There's always like some shit going like we need New York people do that. I like I like I like you
Nick you could sell it for five bucks
You should bury somebody yeah, exactly there's blood all over it
You can sever somebody's spine with that at the base of the neck
Hey, you guys know what a monkey up is
Yeah, you got to be careful with that though cuz I'm monkey up a lot of the girls are underage
You have to be careful with that monkey up. Trust me. I know because I got in trouble with that shit
Look, hey, what's up?
Look at this character
character we'll see a character
you got your shirt
no i told you last time i saw
cuz chris k he parked in the same spot
okay listen don't talk to me
it's crazy
i saw him
he parked out there
he was out there
is that a matter
okay
i like your
i saw him
okay and then
hit fran k
yeah i know
You telling me?
I don't talk like that.
Do you think I talk like that, Chris?
He does improv.
That's what that is.
Improv.
Wait, that doesn't sound like that.
Ha ha ha.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Do I sound like that?
Really?
Do I really sound like that?
Oh my god.
No, listen, the last time I talked to Chris,
he was parked up front.
And I told Rachelle, I was like, he was out there.
because I saw him pop a tire up.
So I had, you know, I told him, I was like,
I saw him out there, okay?
And I, you know, and he's popping his tire.
You can't tell me
This is gonna be fucking
Christmas psyche together for a week. Oh my god, imagine that already they wouldn't need the house
They would fuck each other to death all day all day every day
I'm over each other with a crowbar
You can't tell me I saw him, you know, I don't tell me Michelle
Okay, Michelle, listen, hey, why don't you call your mom then?
If you're gonna call your mom, I told you he was out there probably tired.
Put him on the big screen.
Come on, go ahead, do that, Chris, do it again.
Grumple screen.
Just one more.
Pick up your shirt.
Yeah.
Well, yeah, I told you.
No, he brought his friend.
No, Chris was out there.
He was, because I saw.
He was at he kind of washed his car. I guess he talked to the neighbor. I don't know
But yeah, we're so don't talk to me because I already told you I saw you know
That's his inner gay. That's supposed to be me Chris. I'm offended. Yeah, he's a little gay in that one. Yeah
It takes a lot of effort, you know me, but yeah, that's clean right embrace your gay self Chris
Like Chris, I like that a lot. That was great
Sesty as fuck. I think I just turn more gay
Well, no
Cris, you gotta come to your bro. You can get an acting job tomorrow for like 5k a day with that skit
You just did you call him
Yeah, but that you know that it's not a mess meff. Hello. Well, not a method actor
I said I said I said I said
when I think about it.
I have this one right here.
Like this one.
Here we go.
Take off your shirt.
He's like, no, no, look, look.
Hey, listen.
No, I bet you those are the ones I don't make.
I bet you the, oh man, you make me walk.
I gotta get my medication.
No, I told you, they're three and a half inches.
Yeah, you make me better at you.
Oh.
God I don't walk like that
No, I got it. Oh shit, I gotta get my medication
Hey Tina
I'm about to. Oh, no, no, no, hold on. I got it. I got it. Hold on. That's how he's going to walk up the side. He's done with him.
Yeah. Here you go.
No, he's funny. He's a good actor, bro.
It's 12. It was 12. Fuck all right. I got you.
You're going to make it.
I'm starting to get. What are you doing? You look like you're having like a convulsion
or you're it's better when I imagine I saw pregnant pink when waddling quick to their
Like, let me get through here real quick, you know?
That's what they do, they're the fucking thing, like,
they're not gonna get through McDonald's.
Oh, my God, psyche.
And between you guys and fucking dumpster diving boy
and me and God, I'm fucking dying right now.
I mean, you guys have seen that shit, like these fools fucking, oh my gosh.
Oh my gosh.
You're driving a big car, like a big wheel.
It's like, fuck, chill bro, like McDonald's is right here.
You're gonna fucking rush by me, you know?
This is what Texas is looking for to be like, I don't want to have it.
But yeah.
Hey Chris, you have tattoos on yourself? You have sexy tattoos? Here we go. Just show me your tattoos.
He's fucking winded. Yeah, it takes you know, you have to like get into the zone type shit, you know
Yeah, I don't think I've seen this look
Here I gotta get it down here. Oh good lord. Let me take a look watch
Look at all the fucking mirrors. Yes
Nick Johnson stop stop parking in the handicap spot
What is that bag full of bag of meth
They all want a hamburger
What man, I got these burgers man. Hey, I want a cheeseburger
Hey, come on man. I'll suck you dick. I know you go with this one
Yeah
I have
Look you I literally have a
That's from a movie that's from on menace to society. Yo, you want a cheeseburger? There's a cracker in the alley
He's like you got some rock you got some go
You think that is hit the hit the link my man come on join the party
I know you're a little more reserved than us, but we got to break you in buddy get up
You think that is you here tomorrow night about 10 30
What did I stutter motherfucker? Did I stutter? Well you afraid to come to the table at night?
You ain't afraid to have a black man steal for you. Are you is this black voice? Hope you find your way down Compton Avenue mother fuck
Going down Compton Avenue
Yeah, be here tomorrow night about 10 30
When he steals the cars the guy the white guy comes with the car the maximum picture and he's like you want this
That's my favorite scene
Have fun walking down Compton Avenue motherfucker. What did I study what you were afraid to come to the same hood at night?
Wow
Take your ass back to the West where you belong, you know, there's Hollywood know about this guy
Know some white guy comes to this roll neighborhood site
It's the funniest scene on earth the widest little nerd comes with a picture because he wants a car stolen
So he goes to the hood to have the black kids steal it and some guy opens the door and he looks at the picture
He's like, yeah, so he's a maximum time. That's tomorrow. He's like come back tomorrow
And then the white guy was like tomorrow like he didn't think they could steal that fast and he was like, yeah
Did I start a motherfucker you ain't kid?
You're scared of the black man still for your funky ass is your
And he started like kicking him to get the fuck out of here for walking down Coppin Avenue motherfuckers. Yeah
Wake your punk ass up and that's it though. He's like, oh, yeah, I'm gonna make some shit
He's like fuck your mama. He's like, yeah, I fucked your sister. He's like, hey, hey, what up, what is this door?
And the guy's like nothing much. Bro, what about when they're watching the replay the movie of the robbery?
Hurry up and buy I feel sorry for your mother and they kill the Chinese clerks
And then they steal the video tape the footage and now they're back home drinking 40s watching it laughing
And making fun of each other. He was like look at Kane in the corner drinking at 40 like a sucka
I told you stop showing the mother fucks like a sucker. Hey, stop trippin on the chape. I'm gonna make $59.95 on this
Yeah, exactly. Yo, you're funny. Listen, this one here
Came into the store just to get a beer came out our robbery and excessively murder
It's crazy like that in the hood. Sometimes you never knew what was gonna happen or when
After that, I knew this guy is a
peckerwood. That's why I find
them attractive. Yeah. So cute.
Hey, why don't you give my home
boy a change? I don't want any
trouble. Just get out. Can't
stay. It's your age. I feel
sorry for you. What do you say
about my mama? You feel sorry
Don't watch it. Yeah, that's what got them killed that one little line pop pop
Exactly, I feel sorry for your mother. He was what you say. Hey, where's the motherfucking tape?
Pop your punk ass, too. Hey, hey, hey, clean the cash register
It's got me money somewhere. Oh
Look at pain in the corner drinking a 40 like a sucker
Well, I'm murdering now. Why are you?
Rip and bite
Hurry up and buy it. Yeah
Chris can we play it? Can I play that video of you you gain that fight? Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, okay. Hold on
Breaking you by
Yeah, I mean like what I would like you guys give me something I could try to like imitate like acting talking
To Indian
was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was it was
I got it. I got it. I got it.
Ready? Hold on. I'm going to
share the screen once I get.
Oh, thank you very much, my
friend. Yeah. Thank you. Come
again. Thank you. Come on.
We're going to watch the clip.
Yep. Oh, my god. $3,000 and
generous benefits. My midget.
$5 Buster Knuckle sandwich.
Sweet potato. It's a perfect one. Is he got ads on it? Come on, man.
Hey, don't get this you fucking fool, partner. You better check yourself.
What are you doing, buddy? I ain't no pussy.
Now, do you know what camera is for all that? I ain't no crook.
Well, you better check yourself.
I don't give a fuck what you're talking about. Check yourself, partner.
Hey, partner.
Hey.
You can't brush it.
What gang I
where now
now
I mean full service walked away
you don't know
I bet
now what
bet that
you don't want nobody out there
you know what I'm saying
get that on there
bet you don't want nobody out there
now what
I'm not going to go. I'm not going to go to jail for you.
What the fuck?
You broke this shit!
You wanna get your ass over there?
Get your ass over there!
I'll get your ass over there!
Fucking block out!
I'm not playing with you!
Now what?
Now what the fuck?
What the fuck?
Was that like lagging? Was that lagging though?
Yeah, I was lagging.
I'm on my end.
Eat cater!
Fuck you, Digger! Get the fuck out of here!
Eat cater! Yeah!
Fuckin' all that shit! Got your ass laid down, bitch!
Got your ass laid down, bitch!
Now what?
Anyways, kinda embarrassing, but yeah, it is what it is.
You know what, thank you for letting me play it, it was, oh, I think it was, didn't it?
I was like, you know, I was like, you know, Lowell's, you guys know what Lowell's is?
I don't know. He's an IP2 streamer, like he came out to Vegas, I was just with Lowell's,
he was streaming on kick, he like paid for me to go to the high roller, which is like the,
that meant like the fucking uh, fuck, you know, stupid.
Big yamblers?
The fair, like the Ferris wheel, but it's not a Ferris wheel,
it's fucking like pods that fucking, you know, go around it,
and you can see like the whole city touch it.
He paid for me to go, and like when you're in there,
like there's a bartender, like fucking, I got fucking like,
I probably drank like seven shots of whiskey the whole time.
I was like, boom, boom, boom.
It's free, as long as it's like moving,
like you've unlimited alcohol.
I just I always like just let me get shots of whiskey dude like we you know
Everybody was just drinking like crazy cuz like you know once it once it stops
The high roller once of the Ferris wheel stops like you know
That's it, you know like I was like boom boom
So I got I started drinking like hard shit, dude. This motherfucker was at the goddamn bus stop this fucking the guy I
Thought he was mad dog. I mean you know I'm like looking at me
I was like what's up homie? What's looking at dog type shit, you know me?
You know what you mean homie? I like what's fuck you what you mean? That's how that song gets started
Yeah, I was all drunk and I fucking yeah, I missed that I missed that right and then he like he hit me with a left
Like he was it you know, he hit the right and it kind of did kind of like rung my bell
But like the main thing like fucking I twisted my knee. I
Twisted my fucking knee dude and like I like I saw stars from like my knee
I was like oh my knee and I fuck that's why I backed up. You know me and
Like literally fucking like two three weeks after that bra was the limping on my leg because of my knee
And the punch didn't do nothing, you know, kind of like wrong my belt, but like I twisted my knee and I was like
I kind of like that's my step back. I was like, oh my god my knee and then yeah, so that's why I left. Yeah
My knees good now, but yeah, my fucking if you look at the video go back and look I fucking I twisted my fucking knee
It's suck my knee got fucked up not my then not my face, you know
But yeah, so grab the room in the street
What's up, you got a beer should have body slamber yeah, I could have done a lot of things, but yeah, I fucking uh
You know, I mean it's better off dude like fucking
I don't know if this guy's gonna call the cops like I left right after that
You know, he was on his phone like I was like do you call the cops on me type shit like I'm not gonna get arrested
Much money you make off that
Wow that video made at least 10 grand you got nothing
Yeah, let me try fucking like put it out there. I mean, it's fine
But yeah, I mean
They show the you see the ten one
Yeah, you play the top one. Hold on. It's only played a thousand times. You guys have seen it. So don't play things
You see it. I don't play it play it
We need
I think that I think the ten ones better type shit. This is the directest commentary. Yeah, here we go
Hold on here. Yeah, I like the commentary for one second.
Yeah page page just in time to watch this
Oh my god, is that my page? You come back page you come back
Page get up here, baby. I haven't heard that voice in so long that I'm starting to
Folded during one of Chris K's live fucking with your tent occupied by a homeless individual
This is in the video. Chris K is seen harassing the man by impersonating a police officer
Claiming to be with the Metropolitan Police Department. Let's see what happens. They want to fight me. I'll fuck it. I'm ready
Excuse me, sir
The Metropolitan Police Department can come out. Did you knock on the tent? Oh, yeah
What are you doing over here? What's your name, sir? The homeless man emerges from his tent
It becomes evident that the homeless man is upset by the ordeal Chris K seemingly unfazed by the distress
He has caused continues to taunt the man
Asking if he was scared and refusing to acknowledge the severity of his actions
Hey, what do you can do about it?
Tensions escalate and the homeless man expresses his displeasure at being filmed without consent.
What are you going to do about it? You're homeless.
Rather than showing remorse, becomes confrontational, daring the man to take action against him.
The situation quickly devolves into a near physical altercation, with Chris Kay backing down only after the homeless man grabs the camera.
You can do shit what yeah, you want to press me
Bitch
Fuck you dude
You can do shit
Looks like you won't let me let me put my camera down hold on
Hey, I don't want to fuck with you dog, okay, so no record without asking so don't record me
I'd ask I want a public sidewalk homie. I can just grab you chill
Throughout the encounter, Chris is characterized by a lack of empathy and respect for the homeless man's dignity
Despite being urged to apologize, he adamantly-
But yeah, once he grabbed my shit, my phone is like worth like, you know, a thousand dollars type shit, and I thought he was gonna break-
Don't be the pointy people, don't ask him!
Please!
Chris, you know what's gonna be you next week.
Alright, chill. Did you do anything to strike him?
Alright, I'm not gonna say anything, but yeah, don't fuck my shit up, please, chill.
Apologize.
Hey, but it was apologize
This is IRL baby
Mind your fucking business. Apologize
I was wondering the same thing guys like why am I looking at a dirty toe? Yeah, you need it
But why are you going to ask me walk away walk away, but apologize for all your insults
Man the world's in trouble, bro. We need more love man. He was conquering
That's why I'm playing on your way
Spiritual warfare
You read the Bible?
You know what's funny about this? A psyche is more turned on after watching it
It's like he's showing a dildo in his bar right now. He loves this shit.
I was like, he's the homeless guy.
The live stream abruptly cuts off, leaving viewers with no reservations.
You guys doing an act, is he doing any potential consequences?
That's why you'd be like, on cams for a minute and come back,
or sweaty, fixing his hair, like, haha.
You didn't say you knew what he was doing.
What the fuck?
Poor cat school, they gotta witness that.
That's why those cats look traumatized.
Like, you don't know what it is.
Holy shit.
Meow, meow, meow.
That's a classic Chris K moment
You know doing that shit, but like fucking I'm so tired of homeless people like fucking I gotta like
Hold to a gas station. Here's a homeless guy like look at me like is he gonna grow bad me too dick
I fucking kick him in their face when they ask me for a dollar and laugh like I only carry hundreds there's no
They're gonna kick you out. Do you have a dollar sir?
I only carry hundreds and they kick them and keep walking like I was saying earlier, bro
And you're fucking you're choosing to be homeless like there's programs you can go to that get clean off your fucking fuck met
I would understand if you're fucking homeless like off some bomb-ass fucking met
But I've done the meth out here, dude
Like you're so dumb you like you fuck I want to be homeless to smoke bunk bed
Like you deserve to get woken up at nine o'clock on the sidewalk. Fuck you homeless guy
Get the fuck out of here. Do you make in the city look stupid type shit? You know, that's it
I almost fucking got into a fight with a homeless dude the other day because I go to the gas station like same one because it's in my
Hood and one day I see the guy can you help me tell sir?
I give him a couple dollars the next day seeing guy. Can you help me sir?
Couple days later go back the same guy. I was like, yo, bro. What are you my kid? I don't fucking support you
I almost put him in the chokehold
Thank you
What the fuck I got my own shit to deal with bro. You're not my fucking kid the fuck out of you
Yeah, and they fucking they almost like these almost feel like almost a man like fucking they like fuck you like fuck
You know you give me money fuck. I got a quarter. Oh, no, I don't fuck you then like fuck you did like you know me
So, yeah, like, welcome to the show, everybody.
Our BBB is here.
So, yeah, you know, fucking...
Guys, can you flex for me?
Flex?
Yeah.
You're up.
I mean, I got a, you know, pretty decent...
There you go.
Thank you.
You want an arm wrestle?
Yes, I do.
You're lucky I don't remember who you are cuz they said on like case or beat us panel not too long ago
Like you didn't know where is this someone said it someone shot you out. I'm like, no, that's reason and it's somebody
We know close. I forgot who fuck it was
You know, like I said, I regret both those those clips those situations. I feel like I fuck an asshole
I feel like fucking embarrassed type shit, you know, but yeah
You're born again Christian now, right?
reflection, right
It's fine. It's like we don't embarrass about things that we change ourselves, right?
And it's like I don't think you do that again right today, right?
Yeah, I mean it's like
It's not worth it. It's not worth it to like, you know bother people just I mean, yeah
I mean, that's fucking uh, that's why you know, that's why I hardly stream bro
Like I have my rumble channel and I do like, you know the the the monthly fucking
Requirements to get like maybe 200 bucks
Because I'm a creator I'm rumble
Yeah
You have a creative program where you have to like do like 30 hours
through the studio
You have to have like a certain amount of like a watch views and like certain amount of people in chat
They get there's nothing bar like a bar. So you have to go through you do like five hours of premium
Which is like only people that have premium on rumble will be able to see it and what else what's your channel name on rumble?
I mean it's right there like you rumble is basically YouTube and you don't have to show you found out in five seconds wait a second
Chris hey, Chris. You know how to do websites user Chris K Buster. Okay. Yeah
I mean, it's like yeah, I'm I fucking shit. Yeah, you know how to do websites psyche needs somebody to do websites
I mean, yeah, I mean, you know, nowadays it's like really easy. It's like a fucking template type shit. There you go
Part of it, I mean a programmer
Like guys, what do you think about all these channels that are AI and make money with two million views?
Subscribers a lot of those channels are just AI
People go on their computer. They just like what you're doing
I keep but feel like a bigger level you clip something on newsfeed like Iran is bombing this person
You clip it, then you put AI over it
And then you know with the prompts and you saw another clip another clip another clip and now you have a news channel
People making names of those they're there just
Tech and the three are tech and news and I forgot the other one the three topics Mason you there Mason, where'd you go?
Mason come back
Yeah
Where'd you go?
God why'd you ask where I was a?
VV that was just for content, bro
Like I don't do that dude type shit
I did that for the you know the content for the fucking livestream
I
The reason why I left is because
Alexander was like picking on me and stuff like that. I didn't want to
I didn't hear that I'm picking on you my friend. That was me tickling you a little fancy. Oh, let's say it was a grab one shirt
You want me to pick on you? I don't you know come on. I'm trying to be nice here with the one shirt, man
You know try me friends
We're gonna make you a man
Did you call you a pecker with Mason when I found you Mason you a piece of play though when I'm done with you
You're gonna be a fucking brick
God he was saying stuff to me that I couldn't believe so that's why it's left because I didn't know how to deal with
Where'd you go Mason he left
God yeah, I thought you got you got you. I thought you knew I left. Yeah, so like I don't know what's wrong
But Mason Mason, where'd you go? I?
Just left man
Yeah, but you went somewhere
Where was he here before like hours ago? I remember
No, God, I wasn't anywhere else. I was still like around. Oh, you didn't go anywhere
No, but you let me sit Mason tell us like you to shut the fuck up. Let it out
Tell them shut the fuck up psyche. It's gonna feel good, bro. Trust me
No, me to shut the fuck up. See Alex shut the fuck up
You got no shirts
Psychi I don't really say that kind of stuff
Don't hold it in me so you're gonna rub like a volcano let it out
Psychi, I'm not one to be psychic. I'm not one to be mean so I don't like to like be mean
He doesn't like to be mean Alex
Nobody thinks you're mean Mason bro. Like you're good dude chill. We're good. We're all good, you know, right guys
Nobody's tripping on you bro, like welcome back I guess, right?
Chris Chris K wait Chris K when I asked you like earlier to play video games. Why you say you don't play video? I
Mean my favorite all-time video game is World of Warcraft
And they said you have to be mean in this world because it's a mean world
Yeah
No, I haven't been that way in my life. I'm not I'm not one to be that way
So thank God you matter says so I'm gonna turn you to a man
We're gonna change that shirt. We're gonna put some gel in that hair some glasses on that face get you a channel
You're talking pussy. You're gonna be telling me to shut the fuck up
Do you want to do it? do you want to do a do you want to do a do your own channel though?
I'll help you get started
I have a video uh, well, it's on it was I was on discord. I was on discord and uh, I bought a hooker right here
And I was an asian bitch and I had she uh, I bought one uh, I've heard like jacking me off uh right here type shit
Yeah, she got into it
Joe's comes in at the best moments
No, listen, it's a long story like fucking I I wanted to get a you know a hooker to come fucking
You know my dick or whatever
I called it I called it the picture that I fucking saw was that some skinny like Mexican girl, right?
And she came out she's she's like wobbling up the stairs
Oh, and she came in I'm like hey, I'm sorry
You know you fucking had to come out or whatever like you're not like what the picture shows
She's like talk all she's like look who's talking or whatever like yeah
Here's 20 bucks like sorry for your Uber like leave and I got the next chick as an Asian. I brought her over dude
I was like damn this she's skinny fucking some titties. He's like man. He's such a titties
Yeah, like I just a video out there. I don't have it, but yeah
Fuck you know, I had you know, she everything I wanted to do. I was like fucking I was like, okay, so
You know, she's like, you know, you know, you know, she's like, yeah, so I fucking she started jacking me off
Broke out the lotion
Jacking me up more. I was like, man. I was like, can I feel your titties up or she's like, you know, 100 bucks
Whatever, so I was like, okay. I was like, okay, so I had this yeah, we stopped
Cash after the next hundred so like she's like now. I'm fucking feeling her tits as she's jacking me up. You know me
This whole thing's a lie
Dude nobody's you know nobody's paying a hundred bucks for that I paid like 300 dude
I think the hundred dollars for you to come out here another hundred for to jack me out with another hundred
Yeah
You want you want to like you know
Have sex with my pussy like 500, I was like, fuck, but yeah, so I didn't do it.
Well, I mean, now I've been like almost $1,000, I mean, come on.
Yeah, you already paid her.
Got it.
I mean, I mean fucking I got I got rubbed out and I got to feel like there's just some those are like really nice
Wow, Chris Chris really made all like a bandit. Yeah. Yeah, Mason. I got I mean
He's talking about like a hooker like being with a hooker. Yes. Yeah, but
I was like, hey, come to my house. Don't have another my phone. I
Shit right now
Call her up right now
You fucking cash that means like fucking I'll do it. No, let me talk to her. Call her up. Yeah
Let me let me fucking break her down. I still have her
I was like, I'll get back to you. No fucking up. You know, I got yellow fever
I like I want I want to fuck Asian pussy right now. Oh you me. You know you me so
Get you me in here
You know I've never I've never fucked a I want it fucking Asian bitch like I've never fucking you know
And I want to hear like fucking I like
As I mean like that's what I want
You know, I want to do that. You know what?
Yeah. Oh, me so horny. Oh, I want to hear your fucking.
You know what? You know what?
I
Fuck your mind man. You're paying for all that pussy. You're not fucking you're out of your mind
Yeah, I fuck it. I got ripped off. I think you three hundred
Extra money, so I was like I didn't give a fuck. I was like fuck you only fish tacos like you could have bought with that money
Jesus
Yeah, I still I fucking I still fucking those cities were like I was like I because I was like are they implants I thought well
She's jacking me off. She's like, no, we're gonna hook you up with you me. I was like no way. These are fucking perfect
Like there was like I was
Mason Mason and like that story left I was like I need you to like get on my ride my dick real quick type shit
You know I mean, but yeah, so she said no
No, I mean I would have to pay more money
That's what they put you
I literally had to stop
I was like going limp
Let me cash out to you 100
Send you my fingerprint on there to verify
Yeah, it was dumb dude
Yeah, so
Well, you know what
Cash app is now
I'm letting you borrow a few bucks too, like it's pretty cool.
Hey Chris, can you do that walk again?
Paige didn't see it.
I think she just came in late.
That one?
That walk?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You can do the game voice again, I want to see it.
Paige, check this out.
Check this out.
Watch it.
It's just so great to get an active actor here.
I told you, it's 12 inches.
Take one of this.
My back.
Hey, you got my medication, my knee's going out on me.
Oh, my God.
Is that supposed to be a gay guy?
Wait, what's happening there?
What are you doing?
I don't know.
What is that supposed to be?
I don't get it.
What is it supposed to be?
A gay guy?
A fat guy, dude.
You know fat people like, okay, let me get by here.
Let me get over here.
So, you know, five people, like, they're walking.
I mean, there's our arms are like blown up to their, as their head is.
You know, funny thing is, that sounds like he walks down the street, too.
Yeah, that's how I walk down the street every day.
It's not fast.
Little skip action.
Chris, are you making fun of me?
Come on, stop it.
Yeah, I know we do that
A pillow like under my shirt, but I don't want to stretch this shirt, but yeah imagine like a super fat belly
What do you mean pillow? You're fucking halfway there. Well, there you go
Yeah
It takes a lot of energy to do that do these though
You know, it's like a
Look
Wow
I'm speechless. Okay. Yeah. I'll check it. I already told you
Okay
Well, no last yeah last time I told you was 24 make me check it again. Hey, wait a minute. I need
Get my knee out
The tape measure it. Yeah, it's 24
I told you my back, my back's going out.
Hey Tina, I told you my back.
You got my medication?
Let me get, let me get it.
Wow.
That was good.
Yeah!
Thank you.
you're gonna make me throw my knee out again
Chris, are you stalking Crystal Marie with a gang?
What's that about?
Yes, I was, I'm sorry
No? No comment?
Wait, what? Are you asking me?
I'll tell you what it was about, pal
that Crystal Marie is packing a toavin' sausage
Like, my theories are right
My man wants a piece of that action
Guys, let it out.
Crystal Marie is a training, right?
Why is Crystal Marie saying that you were, like,
with the quarantines with the USOs?
And it's, like, unalive for her.
What was she saying, man?
Wait, hey, where's she at?
Is Crystal Marie live?
I don't know where she is.
Crystal, come on up if you want.
Yeah, come up.
Crystal, what's up?
I haven't talked to her for a while.
I
Somebody save me from this torture the bitch a guy or not man
Crystal marine
She is like yeah, all right
All right, I'm back in love with her. Thank you Chris, you know, 30 diamond though 30 diamond, you know, 30 diamond
30 diamonds 30 diamond flour she
Is it like a is it like a streamer or some shit? Yeah, she's a streamer. I
Mean suss one there, but yeah, I don't know. Yeah, probably not
She's a diamond in the rough
You know LD right yes, that's my homie bro, did you guys hook up in Vegas?
You may be maybe maybe not touch it. You know me, but you made you a man in Vegas
I'm jealous now. I'm not fucking jealous. You guys never know what type of shit. You know what I mean? I'll ask him right now.
You hooked up with LD? I don't want to hook up with you anymore. I didn't hook up with anybody. You know what I mean?
I'm just fucking around. That's my friend, dude. Fucking...
I miss him bro. Listen, I got he's a punk rocker. I got along with them really good dude and get the move get the move
Back to New Jersey like
What do you mean he's right here right now
Yo, God psyche and Chris K. I got a run for a few if you're still up
Hey, you're the homie bro you too man, please
Very fun Alex is cool. That's the chat doing it. I like him. He's from New York, man. He's cool. Yeah, yo, what's up, Tony Alex?
Hey Chris K want to do some DP do some what DP double penetration
Yeah, I mean we need a chick right core. Oh, yeah, of course or like, you know
a real doll. You'll get your
Asian girl. Yeah. You can get an Asian hooker.
Hey, hey, chat. Listen, chat. Fuck you, dude. Cam up.
You know what I mean? Type shit, bro.
Of course you'd be friends with LD. What do you mean, dude?
What does that even mean? Fuck you, dude.
Yeah
Me and LD were fucking like fucking tight as fuck, you know me fucking uh
What's great, you know, it's great, you know, actually I'm not even I'm not even gonna talk about that cuz I'm on YouTube so
Did you beg your sister?
No, but I don't know his sister is a Bobby Dylan the porn star. Yeah, I know
And I every you know, I mean not every time I talked to him but like the first couple times
I was like, bro, can you call I was like, can you call your sister dude? I'm a fan and he's like he like fuck
You know, I was like, oh my bad. My bad. Never mind
So I stopped
I've seen Bobby Dylan in chat, dude, I thought I've you know, I've jacked off to her fucking porn
That's kind of weird that you there you go psych now. You know what to do. Hey, no, I'm a Bobby Dylan
I'm a fan dude like but she's like retired type shit. She's good. I think she has a kid now
Getting married in about two weeks. Yeah, I mean when she's she's lived in Vegas like when when I like
Eight years ago or whatever like fucking I was in Cali and like she was like at the time. She was extreme
And she was working at sapphires and I was like I would I would like go into her stream
Like hey, I want to get a lap dance from you. She's like yeah, come on down sapphires like eight to midnight
Or never like you know me
Yeah, that's it. How was it? I did I never went I never went never went. Yeah
But she knows who I am because I'm up whenever I see her in chat
She goes like good times chat for some reason
This is a typical
Yeah, and I'm like I'm like
Look at a Bobby Dylan on porno up. Do you guys a typical IP to suck a mean they're all like this guy
You know back when she was doing
Back when she was doing the board is she like she was like Finn
She wrote dick hard type shit, you know, so I was like, but you know, I used to check off
So what I want to go to fucking
You know convention the adult movie fucking can get to
It's like I like right here like literally oh Chris do you have a stroke I've been there. I've been to one
Yeah, I want to go dude. I want to fucking get like you know
Some autographs so some of the porn stars. I like you know, so I'm in the porn dude. I like watching porn
I'm a I'm a I guess coming up her
Chris instead of going in harassing homeless people why don't you go with harass women maybe you get one
Women don't like to be harassed usually do they yeah, I mean that's they're called cops. Oh, that's it the cops. Yeah, I
Not trying to harass bitch, you know chicks though, but yeah
Yeah, I don't even scream. I don't mean literally harass dude. I don't mean harass. I mean like go. Why don't you go meet a girl?
Yeah
Here's do you have a girlfriend or wins lots of me to girlfriend?
Maybe he's not into them
a solid girlfriend probably like you may be like a year and a half
But yeah, it wasn't really like I
Don't know. I don't like relationships dude like I just like the fucking I like to fucking get my dick wet and
Get the fuck out of here
I don't want to listen to any fucking shit you got to say
You know where it's like he lives there's a lot of hookers man, you'll be all set
Well, it's just me with like 10 different color wigs
How's that work though, I mean, I mean if I get if I get a chick to get like to suck my dick a hooker
But we're a common like fucking they suck through the cotton
They suck right through it
Yeah, they usually make you unless they're like, you know
Can you imagine how many dicks they suck before you like they probably ate and imagine I have eight. So a hundred thousand
Yeah
Probably a lot
Big good, maybe I just haven't found the right one or whatever dude like I don't you know, I do I do my own thing
so
Like I don't want kids dude. I don't want to bring any fucking look how dumb I am guys right everybody in chat
Look how stupid I am like imagine my offspring
Fuck it probably retarded type shit. Oh, yeah, that's right. It's like he has low self-esteem. You're all set
Yeah, we got it. You know, it's like
So you guys want me to like fucking good to go and have a kid type shit
Yeah, that's easy pickings for you
Okay, I'll make I'll make you a happy man. I will
Yeah, you guys are all tripping out be like psychs like my friend, dude, you know, I just want to like hang out
Maybe like get some fucking beers maybe go to bar
You know who knows what happened, dude, like I'm not trying to like plan anything, you know, so
But you know, I'm not a homophobe like
Get them you're gonna have to prove that to me, right? I do some gay stuff
And I believe you
Right, you know, I have to you don't have to do it. You just have to like have it done to you
You don't have to do anything. You don't have to
Well make my teeth look at my teeth
My teeth I don't have this my teeth look better than that. I'm sorry
Now I don't want to be a turn off
How's that? They're good. I have good teeth, huh?
I didn't say, you know, I didn't say, you know, I said, you know, meet up or whatever, like, fucking, I know that he's fucking gay, you know, I'm not tripping on that type of shit.
I mean, I will read and chat.
Chris, I will be respectful, okay?
Yeah, I'll wait.
I know, dude, you're like, listen, I already know that, like, you are a fucking good person, like, you have a good soul, regardless.
I know in your psychics you would listen. That's why you have viewers right now because people like fucking like you and you fucking you're a good
You know, that's it. I'm 33
So
Yeah, well, so but how's your week Chris? Like I went and when are you moving and stuff?
Shit, I'm like I'm like working on it right now. Yeah
Huh
Do you have $100,000 yet?
No.
Should be at, hopefully, it's $130,000.
Cool.
I mean, I could fucking, tomorrow,
I get a check right now for this spot, $90,000.
Like, tomorrow, if I wanted.
But yeah, I'm going to wait.
I'm going to wait and sell it for more.
No.
You're the one.
Ah!
Look, look, is that going to actually work?
Yeah, it goes by the wrong way. Well on my screen it fucking shows you there
Yeah, that's so gay right there was so gay Jesus, okay
Hey, I go listen, I've been I've been a gay bars, dude
lot I've streamed at a gay bar you know you get hit on in there I imagine you get
yeah I got hit on fucking the guy bought me like three drinks gave me his phone
number everything yeah I was like okay well yeah if you're smart people we
get straight guys that are smart we'll go to a gay bar because first of all
they'll probably get free drinks right you got free drinks you'll have like hot
women there because they go there because they don't get really hit on by
too many guys and then then you'll find some another hot guy too
This guy was, I mean he was cool dude, but you know he wasn't, I don't want to say my type.
He was like square or something?
No, he was like a short, pudgy, like fucking like nerdy like, oh hey, how's it going?
I'm a lot cooler, Chris, I'm a streamer too, so it's like I'm a lot cooler already, right?
Yeah, you know, I'm cute too. Mike. I'm okay. I'm not
Yeah, I mean, just be nice. You know, I'm not gay, but you're you know, you're cool. You're my friend, bro
Type shit. Yeah
Well, you know, if anything did happen, I would never tell unless it was on, you know, you filmed it and sold it to
Amazing
We'll figure it out chatter bait. I think we're yeah, we're gonna be like we can have our own channel
I'm gonna get the IG stuff ready already
Yeah
And we have we can and we can have a
Well, I mean I have a chatter beat. I haven't logged on in like years, but I have one. Yeah, are you've been on it? Wow
I didn't I didn't like show my dick when I got on there and like I had views and I had all like I think a lot of like
Gay males like we're like this should be interesting like they're all typing a chat or whatever like they send me some coins
Yeah, yeah, but you know, it's funny. I was like sitting here, you know, so I've been on it and
It's everyone says they're a woman and it's like basically they're like, oh my god, like I want
My husband to watch us or like or if it's a guy's like I want to watch you with my wife. It's like what the hell
Yeah
There's actually a spot out here in Vegas called the green door
I've heard of that.
Yeah, it's a.
The gay club or not?
No, it's like a, like you said, like couples go there, like married couples go there and like fucking they let their wives like fucking suck dick or whatever type shit like other people.
Yeah, it's like a fuck, you know what I mean?
Yeah, I've never been, I haven't been there, I haven't been there.
Uh, yeah, I'd have to like, you know, I don't, we'll see.
It's that shit, you know, I don't.
Okay, I just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just feeling out the, feeling out the, the only answer.
Yeah, swingers, yeah, swingers, that's what it is.
Yeah, swingers club.
Well, have you ever been to a key party?
No.
If you go to a party and everyone puts their key in a big fish bowl,
and then you just like pick out a key and then like whoever's key you pick out, you, you hook up with.
You could, you could do one of those.
Yeah.
Yeah
What else so how's your tarot going? I've been doing readings and stuff. No, I mean I try to do one
Was it yeah, I was in here with that what was it with that guy with that wanker?
No, it's I did a check for the British guy
You know, I think that it's like it's kind of hard when there's like a lot of people on the panel because like all the energy gets
Because remember you did it like backstage with the guy and you did a really good breathing form
Yeah, I mean I got I mean you almost got to concentrate and focus with the guy and fuck it'll be better
No, it's hard. It's hard to do it like a lot of people watch against everybody's like yeah, everybody's like talking. It's like
I think, I think you do have like, you know, potential, potential, um, to be, oh, here, here. Oh, my cat looks like yours, Chris. Chris, is this?
Kitty cat.
Aw, little kitty.
Oh, look. Looks like your cat, huh?
Aw.
That's a Rudy. Hold on. That's Rudy.
Hi, Rudy.
Hello, kitty. Hey, kitty cat.
Your cat is cute as a little monocle. He's wearing a little monocle.
Aw.
Good boy. He's a sweetheart. He's a that's a big cat right there for 17 years old. Yeah
But yeah, what happens to your beer your beard is like it's a your beard burner. Oh, it's like my beard. Yeah, that's how it always is
It's like it's pretty good look like what?
That you call that a flavor saver or is it like, you know the women like that?
I know I just always just like growing out. I know I
like it
Do you like Fred Durst? You kind of do look like a think of Fred Durst a little bit.
Freaking me out. You wear a mask all kind of things. You're freaking me out. You wear a face.
I came into this world as a reject looking to these eyes. Did you see the size of the flames?
I went to a limb biscuit. I saw a limb biscuit, filter, corn.
It was a family values toward 1989.
Nice. That was a good one.
I feel like one of the last talks that I went through.
It's been a long time, I think my-
It's just one of those days when I don't wanna wake up.
Everything is fucked, everybody sucks.
I really don't know why, but I wanna justify
ripping someone's head off.
Yeah.
I did it all for the nookie.
So you can take the cookie.
The nookie like this.
So you can take that cookie and stick it up, y'all.
Albert, yeah, pretty buddy.
How about this one?
Yeah, I'm gonna do things my way
My little buddy right here. Oh
Hey, you're on the cat that's he's a global cat. He looks just like a really though really look you're gonna get a boy or a girl
It's a male
Well, you can bring your male and then maybe him and Rudy can hook up to
Is she fixed is that a female?
He's fit. It's he and he's 17 years old
Yeah, well fuck
Okay, look look now. Look at that's a cat. It's your buddy right there. You say hi
Kitty cats, oh little kitty cat my little kitty
Yeah
There you go. Oh
I do like him. I do like a guy that looks
Little kiddies. Oh
Okay, guys are we uh, anybody else want to come up and say hi
Get in can you see it is now 120 it's on to it. Yeah, oh
Mason's been emailing me
Interesting it's alright little kitty. Oh
What's it? What's his name? Albert Alley cat
Albert Albert listen now listen you better you better shape up. I'm gonna take you down to the vet to get your vaccinations
Is that fucked up
He looks good. He looks good. Is that my cat?
You better you better fucking not piss on my floor anymore. You want to go to the vet you want to get your shots?
Don't know you better. Oh, he's he's probably a playing bro. That's it. You know me. Yeah, you're gentle
Come on, it's like when you know you have a dog when you have a dog as a pet, you know dogs are like, you know, just like hey
Come here. Come here, buddy. You want to go to the vet? Let's go to the vet, you know
Let me give you a biscuit. Yeah, we'll go to the vet. We'll get your shots
You know, they're like wagging the tail. They don't know what the fuck you're saying is like, oh, they hear your voice
You know, are you in the biscuit jokes now too? Oh shit. Hey, have you been watching beta or anything?
No, but I've seen I fuck that's why I came on your
She was all tripping out on somebody like yelling at somebody like she wanted me like this. She lives in Orange County
Yeah, and like you buy anaheim and I fuck I was gonna like go down there and like hang out like I'm
Let's get let's get together beta. Let's do like some fucking orgy. I don't think beta is
Very happy with me anymore. Yeah, that's this more biscuits August
Yeah, maybe it's kind of mad at me right now. So what would you do man? I didn't do anything and I don't think I did anything
You know, I don't think, I don't, I don't, I don't, I, I, I, I don't think she's ugly, I would hit it, you know.
No, I think she's, you know, she's a beautiful woman, you know.
But, yeah.
She's all embarrassed to like, cam up all the time, you know.
It's like, fuck, what are you embarrassed about? Like, fuck, pop a titty out real quick, you know.
Well, you know, she's not supposed to do that on YouTube, but.
We guys can take up the shirts.
You know, orgy? Yeah.
Well, I'm just kidding.
By the way, I'm just kidding.
Well, yeah, Bita,
actually, I've been clipped with Bita.
You can see, like, a little bit,
but actually, I shouldn't even show it.
I mean, half this chat is all fucking, like,
horny dog-type shit, bro, like, fucking.
You know what I mean?
You know, I'm friends with, like,
you know, like, fucking,
You know
You guys are all fun like a hyped up about shit, you know
It's like it's in a video. It's not like it's like it's like public stuff now
Plus
Yeah, let's just talk about uh, well, we're not gonna talk about
Let's just talk about me. Okay kids. It's a lot. Well, come on
I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I
Mmm, tequila, the, the, the, the, the, the Patron silver?
Hard alcohol? Yeah, I like tequila or like, you know,
I like kind of like mixed stuff.
Like, yeah, I'm kind of a,
I mean, yeah, Patron is fucking smooth as fuck, you know?
I mean, if I drink tequila, that'll be like the only thing,
like the only type of tequila I'll drink.
Uh, yeah, I mean, I'll drink, you know, mostly beer.
But you know, I like you know white Russians the drink. Yeah, white Russians black Russians here with this one of these
Mike's harder
Yeah, that's like what was it a percent. I think it's eight percent or nine. It is right there
Yeah, I mean
Like I don't mean like I don't like to drink beer
And then like, if I'm like, if I'm like, yeah, I'm going to drink tonight, I'll drink beer and then like, I'll switch to like, uh, if I bring a hardship, you know, I'll take shots of whiskey and, uh, but like, well, yeah, white Russians, it's, it's, uh, vodka,
Clua coffee and milk. And when I started drinking the white Russians, it kind of like soothes your stomach, like after you've had like 12 beers or whatever.
Yeah, sometimes it tastes like chocolate like hot chocolate or like, you know, cold chocolate milk
I like when it tastes like chocolate milk, right?
Yeah, I got my neighbors gave me like a bunch of bottles from their like wedding. I'll shoot that big this bottle
I honestly I try to stay away from like I can't like me. I'm fucking up. I'm an alcoholic. I'll admit I
Have to like I don't buy bottles of fucking crown road. That's my shit crown royal
It's so good like fucking I can't buy a bottle Doug if I bring it to my house
I'll drink the whole thing so I don't I don't I don't have any like hard
I'll call like at my house cuz like fucking I don't want you know, I just think I bring beer
That's it. Yeah, the white Russians don't have the clue in it
But that's a black version the white Russians have to half and half
Yeah
We have a little of a casa Doris
Does it have a look like a deer on it?
How's the Doris?
It's a killer.
I drink a lot of coffee, too.
I like something called affacato.
It's like vanilla ice cream with espresso on top of it.
And it's all melted, and it's really good.
Bon.
Yeah.
I love coffee.
I'm drinking.
I actually have half this McDonald's coffee left and my whole I have this one left too. I've been drinking my coffee
I'm a big McDonald's person. Yeah, well that mid cafe coffee is bomb. It's good shit
This one has like five creams in it and it has three things of vanilla
Yeah, that mid cafe is fucking good. It's like, you know, if you want to like wake up that coffee like it's good
Yeah, I fucking know
Let me see, well, yeah, hopefully the chat's doing good.
Let me see, let me see, I don't know how this works.
Anybody does know how to do coding, computer coding?
I need like a coder, it is not like really,
normally they code, but you need to know how to like,
you know, copy and paste, basically.
I'm just like, that kind of coding, like the code.
Yeah, you're trying to like do like a webpage
or something like HTML?
Yeah, what are you trying to do? What are you trying to do web page for bro? No, well
I'm gonna I want to keep it kind of like under wraps for a little bit because I don't want people say like, you know
Oh, it's a bad idea like to go to a short troll. I'm just gonna keep I just be careful
But yeah, I didn't need to like, you know, I want to do a personal website. I'd love to do like a lot of stuff
I'd like to do the troll pedia website
With like a lot of information on it and stuff and also some other I miss my other ideas, and it's just like
Mason's here
Yo Mason
So I can you see the stuff I said to you on your Gmail. Yeah, are you are you watching those?
Yeah
How are they?
They're okay. I wanted you to check them out though. That's why I showed you. I mean I was going to
I was just talking to Chris right now, but yeah, they threw something like that though one woman was going to sleep
Like she wanted me to watch her sleep or something
Oh, it's not weird.
Is he lagging?
No, what was that, Mason?
Is that a transgender playing a video game, the last one I showed you?
A video?
Um, I think it was. Let me see. It says...
What the hell?
Um, let me see.
Aw, kitty cat!
Let me see. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah, I know what you know. Yeah, I think that's a drag queen, right? They call them drag queens. Mm-hmm.
Let me see. I can show a picture of the
Yeah, if you ever met Flurry Diamonds, she's one. Well, not a drag queen. She's more of a transgender.
So like a transgender is a drag queen.
But do you think she's do you think that transgender is pretty?
No, I just like that. She's I like that that person's playing video games though. It's like so like video game
Well, there's a lot of people playing video. I mean, it's like that she she does like what game was she playing?
Did you check it out? So like you like show it to me. I won't have to look right now. I'm looking right now
Log in
Have a look. Okay, so amazing. It's not me
Oh, here he is, okay.
Drag in horror games.
Silent Hill continues.
Let's see what this woman sees.
Oh, I wanna see what Chris K thinks of this woman.
Oh, oh my gosh.
Amazing, amazing, amazing.
I mean, she's a little bit, hold on.
Oh yeah, you know, my cats, I fucking,
I like to like replenish like the water bowl.
I like dump it out and like refill it with fresh water
because I like fresh, you know.
Yeah, well Mike. Yeah, my cat like Rudy like basically jumps in the water and babes
Yeah, but look there's a Mason. I think
Pretty
Yeah, that she is definitely a
Drag queen looks like some bitch you see in Vegas all day. I
Looks like flirty dog with blonde hair kind of do you like that person site?
Um, like, like, like, I'm, like, I'm attracted, you know, but drag queens aren't really attracted to that person.
I'm not really into drag queens, nor transgender.
I'm more into, like, checkerwood.
Well, hey, Mason, are you attracted to that? Her? Him? Whatever? No. No, I just, no, I just like that they're playing video games. I like video games.
I don't know man, but you know Mason if you go to twitch or you go to like kick they play a lot of video games there and they're just like
You know
You gotta like you know if you're if you're just like the uh, you know
No, yeah, this is the last game you gotta lie about it
Yeah, I mean there's no don't need to be embarrassed here. I think yeah
Who gives up, you know, I mean if that's what you like do it like fucking life is short bro
I should do what you do. Do what you want, right?
Sike, so if you like something you like something, right? Don't just like it
I mean don't don't think you have to not like it because somebody else says doesn't they don't like it, right exactly
Yeah, because like a lot of things are just society and like in some some some friends will like, you know
Just be jerks about it and like no, but that's how friends are sometimes. Yeah, fuck people's opinion, bro
Like it's your choice your fucking life. You whatever you think is what happens
Yep, Mason Johnny says you were boxers or briefs
Psyche I
Weren't brief spam, but like I don't get it
Tidy whiteies you wear tidy whiteies or there are no briefs. It's like, you know, they're called briefs briefs
Yeah, but they're called tidy whiteies usually. No, those are boxers. No, they're kind of boxers though. So like
Box of briefs box of briefs. Yeah
They're kind of half and half. Okay
You got a listen you guys were underwear
Do I know do you? I don't know. I do what I can remember too. Let me see. Where'd my camera go?
Drop my camera. Sike, Sike, I don't get what you're doing, man.
He dropped his camera, bro. He dropped his camera. Hold on. I need to find it. Where'd it go?
It's under the couch. Under the couch. Yeah
What's up, what's up, what's up,
what's up, what's up, what's up,
They're big.
Just be honest.
No.
Who cares?
It's okay.
Slaggy.
Do I go commando?
Not really.
I usually wear underwear.
Just sweaty balls.
Yeah.
Haha.
I usually do, you know, sometimes I wear Speedo or sometimes I just, how do the nuggies do it?
Saki, I never, Saki, I never go commando, man. I usually wear boxer briefs. Yeah, like you're talking about.
It's fine. What about when you, do you like go swimming in Speedo?
Nut-huggers are called, not butt-huggers. They're called nut-huggers, not butt-huggers.
Perfectly. I saw Victoria's Secret today at Hollywood and I was like, what is Victoria's Secret?
Chris K, you ever played a game called DOOM before? Like there's a game called DOOM.
Yeah, hell yeah, I played it.
Resident Evil? I've played that one.
Hey, you play drums, Mason?
Yeah.
Fucking uh, you like any punk rock music?
Listen to regular rock. I mean
Psych play the song and lag wagon stoke in the neighbors and listen like this
Just the first like 10 seconds of this fucking this drum solo dude
Okay, you're not gonna get copied right though. I know I know maybe if it is never mind
Lag wagon stoke in the neighbors
And like the first like seven seconds of the first like this is hard. It's so hard
Chris K that's a that's a punk band that you're talking about right? Yeah. Yeah. Hell. Yeah is I've seen him. I've seen him live
My hag wagon neighbors, it's about stoking the neighbors, okay
Okay, I see it stoking the neighbors listen like like right at the start listen the drums
It's fucking badass, dude.
Play this, Mason, type shit, you know what I mean?
Oh, everybody.
Play it again, play it again, play it.
Pretty good.
Hey, Mason, can you do this one?
Can you do this, Mason?
I have a drum set right here.
Where is it?
There you go, Mason.
Can you do this?
Yeah, it's lucky, yeah.
Play that one drum part that you played at the beginning of the song.
The one that he's talking about.
Can you do this
This is hard right this is hard
Not as hard as me
Hey, can you do this? Can you do this? Can you do this? Hey, guys, can you do this guys?
Fucking me now. We started the meme type shit, bro
Let's do this guys. Watch me. Watch me
I bet you guys I bet you can't do this, you know
Hey, hey Mason, can you do this?
Hey, listen, hey, can you do this?
Look what I can do. Look what I can do.
Look, mom, no hands.
I can ride a bike.
Hey, look, this is my, uh, I've seen Pantera dude last week. Here's the ticket.
Oh, yeah, I saw you go to some cool, some cool concerts and stuff.
You know, I saw King Diamond in December with the King Diamond concert.
Five minutes alone.
Can't you see I'm easily bothered by persistence?
One step from lashing out at you.
Really? Spirit? What? What do you say?
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know.
Oh my god. What were you doing
with your hand like that?
No, it's fucking. I'm like
delirious. Tell me. Yeah, I'm
where's the silly tonight? I
like it. I like it. I like it.
I like being delirious. You
know? Is that a real ticket?
Is that it? What are you talking
about? Yeah, hell yeah, it is
not. I see them at T-Mobile
Arena in Vegas. I live in Vegas.
Chris Kate, that's a real ticket you actually got and go once you can see the live concert
Like I can give you my Facebook and Instagram like good on my Instagram like there's the latest picture put it up
Psych the ladies pictures me like at the concert fucking with Pantera in the background like show it
I don't know if you just have it on your phone. You just put the phone up or whatever. But yeah, I will. Okay. I got it. I
Have a buddy out here, dude
He's an Indian guy, but he's like super cool
And he's my concert buddy. He's in the metal and
So yeah, I went with him like I've been to so many fucking concerts in big I think
Have you ever been to a disturbed concert before Chris K? Not disturbed. I've seen slipknot
tool
I've seen tool. I thought I'd pervers with the home. Yeah, that's my latest pick right there. Yeah, Pantera like that's me
Wait show me again. Uh, it's like, show me again
Pantera
Sorry, you can't see that
It's like, why is it blurry though? It looks blurry. I don't know. Okay. It's my phone. It's my tablet
It's Pantera though
Yeah
Yeah, it was kind of weird because like it's hard to like sit in a fucking chair and listen to Pantera
Like I wish I was like on the ground level like by the pit, you know
Yeah, I like the pits at concerts like I
That's what I went to like, you know, you're a bit to wash pit before psych. Yep. They're fun
I was on mushrooms and when I went to the family values tour, this is like 2019 and I and
And then I was corn family values, right corn
That's the most that's that family or that's corn. Yeah, there's corn. It was cornland biscuit
Method man red man filter and some other a couple of the bands. Oh, you got it.
So it was Marilyn Manson there. The group. Man's in a concert several times probably like five times and plus I've met him too.
I used to be a big Manson fan, or you know, I don't like his, he's like kind of old, but I do like in the 90s.
Lots of pretty, pretty ones, wanna get you high.
I've seen a whole Twice in concert, and I've seen...
Now the pretty, pretty ones will leave you low, and blow your mind with all the stuff now in the dope show.
I'm out of a Nancy. Oh, no, no, sorry. That's not
guys my
This is all blurry said film out of his butthole cam. Where's that? What do you mean Nick?
What are you talking about butthole?
So any man site the beautiful site the beautiful people the beautiful people
Yeah, and I don't want you
I don't need ya.
Don't hesitate.
Don't make a big job.
That's always right.
Hey, you.
What do you say?
Something beautiful and something free.
Hey, you.
What do you say?
You live a life spread.
It's all to be made.
Boom.
I used to do meth dude, and I used to like stay up like three nights on meth all and I would listen to Marilyn Manson
I would feel better
Yeah, let me see if I might have any man song like Chris K. Chris K. That's a good song
Come on from Marilyn Manson the beautiful people the beautiful people
Yeah, hell yeah
Okay, well, I can't I don't know I can't find
Hey, listen, what a fucking uh, it's only in the morning. He's supposed to be up cooking breakfast by then
So that's like a long clock. Whoo-whoo
Well, you want to whoo-whoo? Hey?
And they say that's only the morning
The whistle go whoo. Well, you want to whoo-whoo?
Whoop whoop whoop whoop. Hey, we do it for decoration. That's it and that's all we do for decoration, you know
You're doing a juggalo thing
You guys don't know what that is. Come on, man. Hey, it's the whistle tips above Robin little sis play
Look, I listen at the latest rage for kids is driving parents in a tyrant neighborhood is crazy
It's called a whistle tip and it's welded inside the exhaust and it's driving the whole entire neighborhood crazy
Do you want no, I don't want that buddy
This'll tell you what
You know, I just sell, I just sell, you know what, the whistle go, woo!
People are saying too loud, hey, that's only in the morning.
You're supposed to be up cooking breakfast or something by then.
So that's like alarm clock, woo, woo!
Hold on, I got it, hold on one second.
I'm gonna share the screen here.
Watch this, this is the whistle tips, I wanna show you.
Yeah.
Whistle tips, woo, woo, woo.
This is so funny, bro.
I mean, it's funny to me, I guess.
I don't know.
to make the car reachingly loud for nearly a mile.
Well, tomorrow night Oakland residents will be
attending officially the City Hall officials.
This is our one.
Oh, that's a remix.
That ain't a really good one.
Hey, play the original one, though.
That's a remix.
That's a nice one.
Okay.
Yeah, it's in there somewhere like the original original
Damn city residents have been told this noise is perfectly legal. So tomorrow they hope to start the problem
Anybody that has it in their neighborhood it's gonna be totally driven crazy
It's that woo woo
Any chip off the floor masses a decoration man just a decoration that's it. That's all man. We do it for decoration
Some neighbors are saying way too loud that's only in the moment
He pulls me up cooking breakfast or somebody and so that's like a little imply
it makes the car audible for almost a mile some neighbors are saying way too
loud that's only in the morning we supposed to be up cooking breakfast or
somebody so that's like alarm clock decoration that's all man we do it for
decoration
Wait, wait, okay pause it for a minute listen the latest rage for kids is driving parents and entire
Neighborhoods crazy. It's called a whistle tip and it's welded inside a cars muffler
To make the car screechingly loud for nearly a mile
Wait, hold this it do you guys hear me?
Hello
Wait, can you guys hear me?
Hello hello am I locked out?
Listen, you remember when the chicks like yeah, I got one on my car. Look this is how this is how she says it
No, like
Yeah, I want my car. Yeah, she's like, yeah, I got one my car
You got one on here. Yeah, I got one in my car. Play back. Play back that same that same put go back to that
Force is like I got one my car
We'll be complaining officially the city hall officials from force mark jones has the story live in oakland this evening
Pam city residents have been told this noise is perfectly legal. So tomorrow
Change the law
Nearly every muffler shop in Oakland is installing whistler tips.
It's a piece of metal welded inside the exhaust pipes.
That makes the car a little bit mild.
Tell me about the whistles.
The whistles got whoop!
Anybody that has it in their neighborhood is going to be totally driven crazy.
It sounds like that.
It's that woo woo. You know I'm saying then you got the flows any trip are the flow masses a decoration man
It's just a decoration
We do it for decoration in your car. Yeah
Roxanne Bruns is the high-pitched tone like the squeal of a park brake that doesn't stop.
Police have told her it is legal.
They think it's a fad.
Hey, play it backwards or she says she's done.
Real quick, and it's driving you nuts.
It's driving me nuts. I work at home.
I can't concentrate when it goes on for, you know, hours.
Some neighbors are saying way too loud.
That's only in the moment.
He's supposed to be up cooking breakfast or something like that, so that's like a alarm clock.
Woo! Woo!
Both the Russ and Little Sis were probably short off.
If you want to live, they want to stop something.
You want a wrong lane?
And a C transit bus driver told us the noise is so
They've caused no known accident
Parents and entire neighborhoods crazy it's called a whistle tip and it's well
But makes the car audible for almost a mile
Tell me about the whistles
Anybody that has it in their neighborhood. It's good. You think it sounds like her?
Well, you want to woo woo it's that woo woo
You know, see then you got the flows they need to bar the flow masses and decoration man
It's just a decoration. That's it. That's all man. We do it for decoration in your car
Roxanne bronze has the
Bartrain that doesn't stop is keeping her
We do it blows anything about the foam as is a decoration
That's just a decoration. That's it. That's all man. We do it for decoration. You have it in your car
Roxanne Bruns has the high
Bar train that doesn't stop
I go, I go on my car. Yeah, go on my car.
Suck it, yeah. Suck it, yeah. I like it.
Chris, can I whistle on your tip?
Yeah, sure. Yeah, yeah, I go on my car.
You got in your car? Yeah.
It was being installed on your car.
I mean, it's like, you know.
Hey Mason try to do that. Try to sound like the way she talked
So I guess not on my car
Zero effort you put zero effort into that try again
What I mean, thank you, no not on my car
No, she says like yeah, I got my car
You know, she's like, you know, she's like, you know, she's like, they're like, do you have it on your car?
She's like, you know, it was being installed on her car.
We want to whoop whoop, psyche.
No, not on my car.
I don't know about that Nancy like I saw that he was like there's like a misunderstanding or something. I'm not sure. She was like she's like oh something somebody kicked him out of her.
And then he.
He was saying too loud. That's only in the morning. You supposed to be up cooking breakfast or something by then so that's like a long clock.
Woo woo.
Mason can you go whoop whoop.
What do you want to woo woo? It's that woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo
You know what I mean? Hold on a second Mason. Hold on. Let me find some. Yeah
Yeah, I mean that the news actually put that on the news they actually had these guys like fucking peeled out
Went to the other lane ran a stop sign bro tech shit. You know what I mean? That's crazy, right?
Their name is Bob we're like they actually said like if you go back and watch the video it's like in the video in the bottom
It's like bug rub
It says Bob rub
He's like what he's like, you know
Yeah, I'm looking for
Well, here's a woman saying here like this like somebody told me it's like somebody told me that you have a girlfriend that looks like a
song psyche
She looks like what?
Remember that song psyche somebody told me you have a boyfriend that looks like a girl
It's crazy like do you have it on your car and she's like my car they're like it's being installed like she already had it
It's not being installed and she already had it, you know, it's being installed on her car, you know
Yeah.
Just give me one minute.
Well, here's some guy, like...
Oh, he keeps closing the door.
Oh, I'm going to call him.
Yeah, I'm going to call him to my car.
Hey, what's up, Mason?
Mason, where's the thing? Hi.
Yeah, yeah, Chris, yeah.
Deftones do fucking
shove it shove it shove it
So sorry play it so I play us another video. I'm doing it. I'm looking right now. I'm looking right now. Just one second
Nirvana
So like he has a psyche as a guitar. It's like a guitar. Yeah
Some of the disturbances in the video
What the f**k?
later on some objects start flying around the room where the little girl is at
you decide you think it's real or a hoax
who
Jesus Christ
I don't think anything's moving
no way come on
It's like 20, 22, 32, 33.
Okay, hold up here.
Oh, my car!
Serving this car.
Take place.
감사합니다.
Out of nowhere, two armed men appeared behind Cohen.
The streamer lets out a scared gasp, but manages to remain calm, before being walked off-camera
by the two men.
Viewers in the live chat were stunned, with many thinking this was a set-up prank.
Unfortunately for Cohen, this was totally real.
After the two men walked him off-camera, they searched his entire house.
Before the stream cuts off, one of the two men wearing a blue hoodie can be seen.
However, the camera was too low to capture his face.
After the stream cut out, Cohen's viewers were very scared,
thinking the two men might have harmed him or his family.
But the streamer later made a post on Facebook saying that the men did not hurt him or his family,
and instead just took their belongings and car.
He also expressed his thanks for his viewer support.
It was a horrible and scary situation.
But thankfully, Cohen and his family made it out okay.
It was December 2018, a Twitch streamer from Kansas City, Missouri named Tron1717 went live.
But as soon as his stream began, his viewers were already concerned.
He was sitting at the wheel of his car, struggling with his seatbelt and slurring his words.
It didn't take long for viewers to realize Tron was clearly intoxicated.
His viewers began begging him not to drive.
But Tron ignored all of his viewers' concerns, leading to some viewers calling the police,
others in danger. For a moment, everything seems okay until Tron lets out a scared gasp.
He can then be heard cursing just before the stream cuts off.
Understandably, his viewers were very concerned, fearing he might be seriously injured or worse.
Thankfully, Tron was uninjured in the crash.
He had hit a light pole and got a DWI charge.
After his own viewers called the police, Tron also received a temporary ban from Twitch.
Thankfully, in this case, no one was hurt, but things could have been so much worse.
I don't fucking dream to try it, bro.
In 2018, one of the most popular Twitch streamers at the time, Dr. Disrespect, was playing Call of Duty.
Yeah, you know who this house got shot at?
Tens of thousands of fans.
But as he was playing the first person shooter, a shooter would target him in real life.
And Dr. Disrespect has a fucking contract with Rumble.
Causing him to walk off camera.
Ah, man!
Just not finishing!
Yeah, Dr. Disrespect streams on rumble now dude. He has a contract they give him money type shit
Hey back
He was visibly shaken he had taken off his costume and was out of character telling his viewers he had to end the stream
Ladies and gentlemen, I gotta end
I've got it in the broadcast right now so much shot at our house broke upstairs window
This is the second shot so much shot yesterday
At our so much shot yesterday at our house and so much shot again right now and connected with the house
upstairs
Right, you're driving by
Right, you
Dr. Disrespect was visibly irate which is understandable as his wife and child were at home and could have easily been injured or worse months earlier
That's like it's crazy says I fell any type shit, bro. I fucking they they did it so I can kill them, you know
Right
I would test texting and drove into a wall or something
Mondo on a Mondo that I P2 guy, right?
Are you on ip2 chris?
Yeah, I am.
You are?
You're on ip2.
Listen, you know who jewel rancid is?
Not sure.
Who is it?
She's streaming on ip2.
You know what, you know what, Tilla?
Mmm.
Like she's married she's married to a tiller like but they do like a porn and shit like I think I I think
Until I would let me like fuck like fuck his wife
So I think I'm Alexander knows a tiller. I thought she interviewed him. Yeah, I was in a Myers. Yep. Yeah, I was just with her yesterday
Yeah, it's crazy cuz uh today
Oh, do you have a Victoria? Do you know Victoria? Victoria J?
You have to hear this. This chick is like, um, yeah, I'll bring it up.
This chick, she like, is supposedly like this hot girl, but she like, like,
she doesn't sound hot. And then it's like, she lives with her mom and stuff.
You know what I think? The hottest chick on IB2 is, uh, what's her name?
I don't know. What's her name? Yeah, I'm trying to think. Uh.
Help me out chat. It's the
Blanchik.
It was a not not all of she's
all the way around. I think it's
I can take my time. But yeah.
Look at this. Victoria J though.
She got banned. She got banned on
TikTok I guess and now she's
like that. We need to get her. We need to bring her in the
orgy type shit. Yeah. Oh my god. She has like dreads. Like
she's blonde hair. Like she has dreads. Oh, look at this. Go
go my car. Yeah, go on my car. This is so funny. So, we
Okay, I can't forget the interview
Yeah
Hey, you a listen
Psych you want you want to be out you want to get on you know you want to be on IPT network?
Yeah, sure
But I mean, I mean, I don't know it might happen
What she lost weight
This is ai dude this is ai
Hey, this is Brittany Jones your local catfish last
Hunchback of IP to I had to end my stream because she'll buddy try to get a strike on my channel because they're a bunch of cowards a
Bunch of pussy ass little bitches that got
Trying to take my channel down. I have to laugh at that shit
Yeah dude, why don't you see this is um talk shit about blackout now. I don't know who blackout is
What come on, please go fuck yourself dude. You're literally pissed off at me because I called his daddy
I called his daddy and told him that his son is a degenerate piece of shit that makes
death threats on here and docks his people and has an aro against him for a 12-year-old.
Is that it?
You're that butt hurt over me calling his daddy and telling him that his son's a piece
of shit?
Well, too fucking bad.
Go see some more.
Go see a little bit more.
I'm seeing a little bit more. I leave Eric's mom
Go ahead call my mom. Hey fuck it. I'll call my mom right now. Okay, everybody. This is my mom
I'm not gonna her name is Hillary by the way. Okay, so Hillary mom
I just want to ask you a couple questions. Okay, so last night I called the streamers dad
Oh, big base clip says hey mom say hi mom
Say hi to say hi to base clips dude. Come on
Say hi to you, say hi to Bay, just say hi Bay.
Okay, so that's my mom guys. Anyways
All of them
Okay, okay. Thank you mom. Anyway, so he's threatening me. He's starting to doctor your address. He's threatening to block out
Yeah, and yeah, I know I know
Okay, okay, please don't please don't swear anyways, but let me let me tell you
I pulled his father up. I found I
He's got an arrow against him that's a restraining order
Streamer on here and her 12 year old
Hey, your son is
harass me on here threatens to dox my mom is my elderly mother's address you need to do something
and and then everybody's in the chat like
Ask your mom what you do for her to make her feel more comfortable. Hey mom. How do you feel about jay drake talking about?
Sorry
Yeah
Have you heard have you heard of a bam bam?
bam bam
From the Flintstones?
Yeah
It's that for the frist notes, so I'm bam-bam and pebbles
BAM
Bam-bam, right? Like yeah, right there. Yeah, he's like super late
Super strength and he beats up everybody. Oh shit. I need to get my fucking toenails done. Oh my god
So you're watching drag queens now Mason, what's going on?
I'm just checking it out. So I guess it was something that came across my channel. So I'll try to see what it was like
Sure, sure
But you said it to me you think that you think I would like it too. No, it's like I was just checking it out. Yeah
The drag queens are like usually just like entertainers. They're not really like usually transgender
Some people so I go so like why would Alexander say don't make me come up though. That's what he says
Alex what Mason what are you doing? Where you where you from dog Mason?
I'm from Houston, Texas. No shit. I live right near the beach. Bye
I've stayed in Houston, Texas a Chris for a long time around there. Yeah, I'm down right on the beach
Are you in like Las Vegas? That's not by the beach. I'm fucking around. I'm just fucking around
Yeah, you're going to be living by the beach when you come
Let me try to try to say it like you know right near the beach
Try to do it try to say that I don't know they're not they're not
I know I fucking I'm stupid right? I'm brain dead touch it. You know, I think it's funny
I don't know. Oh, yeah, you know you're funny. Hey, so Mason Alex is just a nut
Alice is a little bit crazy Alexander the Queen. He said explain my mentality to Mason
He's a cocaine snipping police officer
So it's like so
So like so what what do you think about all this though like about Alexander saying this stuff to me?
Well, I think he doesn't mean harm. He's like he he says he said he wanted to take me in the bushes and
You know have his way with me and then instead of giving me a ticket he would like you know
Take me into the bushes and stuff
Not against it, but I don't have a car. I would have to be off my
I mean, someone came and do a KO piece, okay.
You know what?
You know what sucks about getting banned on YouTube, bro?
Like, fucking, I lost.
Like, I subscribed to like so many people, dude.
I fucking, I like, when I got banned on YouTube,
I forgot a lot of my subs.
You know what I mean?
Does that make sense?
Yeah, but I mean, it's like,
so they delete your whole account or something?
Yeah.
I rip like 2,000 so I rip gone you can't and you can't start a new account
I don't understand you can't sort of I mean they kind of have right here. This is it, you know
Yeah, but you can't say
Okay, use your money
Say
You don't like you or is it like you just can't be monetized. Let me say I'll tell you let me say that
It's like you can hear me, right? Yeah, period. What?
So I can hear me. Yes, I can sir. Can you hear me? There's a riser 2.0. So left it off. It's just words
Yeah, it is just words and Alice is just a loudmouth. He's not like it's not like he's like your house or something like that
He's just he's all the way in New York. He's like hyper probably like got a big eight ball
Snipped it off the toilet seat and having a good night with us
Tell me can you hear me? Can you feel me?
Tell me Chris Chris case. So you're a musician too just like me
So I played you played a guitar a little bit
You got
Psych have you heard a guitar?
Right sec. Have you heard my songs on a sound club? Oh
Yes, I'm playing one
I raised our video. It's not on my it's like I haven't in my shorts now
To my shorts
Listen, I have two dates punk rock. I have two songs that are on a soundcloud
This joker's name. I'm sorry. Can you take huge L out of the chat? Please?
Alex you get him out. Please delete him
Thank you, you know any kind of that talk is this like automatic
I don't know if I don't know if I'm psyched if you've heard this my shit though. This the song for yeah
It's like site. There's no pedals in here. So I don't know what someone would say pedals
And I don't even see me
What is saying is he's like a he's like a very sad person. Yeah, definitely projected
Because he is a huge loser and probably all those other things to do that he's saying so
That's only people that
that's ever like accuse everybody else of it.
Actually, someone told me tonight,
oh yeah, I did talk to them very wise.
They're like, you should do a lecture about projections.
Yeah.
Because there's like shadow projection
and it's like, most of the time,
people accuse you of something,
it's like them and it's doing it, right?
It's like, so.
Go to SoundCloud and look up Chris K. Buster
and play the song, Fuck You.
It's a message. It's it's it's a it's hardcore punk, dude. It's the song I sing I sing in it. So let me know what you think
Yeah, hey Chris K. Do you like a limb biscuit? Do you listen to him? I mean, yeah, I like him, but I you know, I'm not like
Not like a super fan. Yeah, I don't like listen to him like on a daily type shit
I'm you know, he you know what he when he tours when Fred Durst
Taurus he wears a wig cuz everybody's like Fred. This is so old. There's our shit
Screw your mind, you never know, imagine getting mad at me, because love takes you down, I'm so apart, you fucking face, it's been all over the town.
Okay, that was enough.
Is that too hard for her? Or what?
No, I mean, yeah.
Is that it made me it made me sad. It's okay. Well, hey go to play by the way. That's why it's called fucking mom
Okay, no, I'm not gonna play that okay, but I will play I'm not the end but I know my shit listen
I'm my shit's bolder. I mean, I'm sorry. What is it? I mean, it's like, yeah, I don't I don't like the f-word
It's just like what you know what I think about and that's all right. That's what y'all though
That's what it is. Actually, you know, maybe I have problems texture. You know me
Sorry
Yes, so I guess I'm very nice. Let's say an epi to your mom
Well, no, I have a song it's called fuck your mom and yes, and that's another one
It's on there like play it. Well, you know what I think that
I'm going to get some rest, but I want to thank you, Chris K, thank you, man.
I love you, bro.
Hey, I love you, Cy.
We'll meet up at some point.
Touch it, you know what I mean?
Okay.
We're going to have some fun, Chris.
We're going to have some fun.
Cy, you got to leave now?
You got to go?
I'm going to go leave.
I'm going to go watch that drag queen.
I mean, hey, when you came in Mason, he just, you know, he left.
You fucked it up.
No, I'm kidding.
I'm joking.
No, no, no, no, Chris.
Cy, you know, we're cool, though.
We big.
I'm just fucking with you, bro.
I'll see you the other way up, but thank you guys. I love you. I'll talk to you soon. Okay. Thank you guys
Thank you. Yeah, give me up talk to you soon. Oh shit
came a storm on wheels rolling in smooth with the mafia feels
cuban cigar lit like it's temper pizza in one hand hot dog for dinner said psyche i'm bored
had to switch the scene left some poor woman screaming on live stream trolled her down to
the void and back then crashed my show like a heart attack got it
We friends, forever my friend
He thinks he's God, with a lowercase g
In a wheelchair still stomping through the live feed
Bout of your king while smoking that leaf
Laughing at chaos like it's comic relief
Brought spunky two now that trolls a gem
Cameras glitchin', chat on fire
Mott's beggin' me to cut the wire
But nah, I like my circus, I love this mess
Every troll's just a test, stop the mess
Forever my friend
You called me a fraud then defended my clown
Spam my chat then held it down
You got layers like a deep dish slice
Under all that shade
A heart made of ice and maybe rice so let's light that cigar
Raise the mic another night of chaos welcome to psych
Brought the drama, the heat, the fun, and weirdly, it feels like.
You're the one?
Got it!
Yeah, you crazy but your family!
They dox, they slander, they gaslight, they disrupt.
But what if you had the ultimate guide to shut them down?
Introducing Trollopedia, your field manual to decode, expose, and outsmart internet trolls.
From classic tactics like lovebombing to modern swarm attacks, Trollopedia breaks it all down.
Know the playbook, flip the script, take back your power.
Trollopedia